靠近點
Come in close.
再近點
Closer.
當覺得自己看到的越多
Because the more you think you see,
你就越容易受騙
the easier it'll be to fool you.
眼見真的為實嗎
Because what is seeing?
你的眼睛在看
You're looking,
但其實你是在過濾  在理解
but what you're really doing is filtering, interpreting,
在尋找其中的意義
searching for meaning.
我的工作
My job?
就是用你給我最好的禮物  你的注意力
To take that most precious of gifts you give me, your attention,
來給你制造假象
and use it against you.
芝加哥   星期一
我現在要開始翻牌了
I'm going to flip through this deck.
我要你看清楚一張牌
And I want you to see one card.
不是這張  這張太明顯
Not this one. That's too obvious.
集中好注意力
Pay close attention.
太快了  我再來一次
That was too fast. I'll do it again.
準備好了嗎
Are you ready?
來了
Okay.
-看清一張了嗎                    -是的
- Now did you see one?                                     - Yes.
-記得是哪一張嗎                  -是的
- Do you have one in mind?                          - Yes.
這其中有那張牌嗎
Now, do you see your card here?
沒有
No.
因為你看得太仔細
That's because you're looking too closely.
我一整晚都怎么跟你們說的
And what have I been telling you all night?
看得越仔細
The closer you look,
看到的越少
The less you see.
新奧爾良   星期二
看著我的眼睛
Now look into my eyes.
沉睡吧  好了
And sleep. Okay.
現在... 你要能把這鈔票從我手上拿走  這錢就歸你了
And... If you can get this bill from me, you can have it.
來吧  拿去  過來拿
Go ahead. Take it. Get it.
或者說出你自己的名字也行
If you can say your name, you can have it.
你先站那兒緩一緩
All right, just hang out there, wriggle a sec.
-我要偷窺一下你老公的大腦              -不不不
- I'm gonna take a little peek under the hood of your hubby's brain.      - Oh, no, no, no.
-我看到了... 別告訴我                  -當然
- I'm picturing... Don't tell me.                                 - Of course.
沙灘  雞尾酒
Beach. Cocktails.
-佛羅裡達嗎               -聽著  那次是因公出差
- Florida?                          - Look, it was a business trip.
某種意義上的公事  也許是最陳年的往事
I mean, it is a kind of business. Maybe the oldest business.
-那個...親愛的...我們...          -她現在動不了  麥克
- You know what, Honey Bee, let's...               - She can't move, Mack.
你在想一個女人的名字
You're thinking of a woman's name.
A  B  C
A, B, C,
D  E  F  G
D ,E F, G,
H  I  J
H, I, J...
J嗎  金  簡  詹尼特
J? Jean. Jane. Janet.
誰是詹尼特
Who's Janet?
你認識詹尼特嗎
You know Janet?
不是你的閨蜜吧  是嗎
It's not your best friend, is it?
-你的妹妹                  -不  別這樣
- Your sister?                                            - No, please.
她的妹妹  我的天啊
Her sister? Oh, my God.
你不是因公出差
You weren't away on business.
-你是因詹尼特出差        -不
- You were away on Janet.              - No.
你老婆的妹妹
Your wife's sister!
我們得挪過來一點  因為她現在看上去有點惱火
Okay, we need to move over here, because it seems like she's a little bit upset right now.
你想讓這一切都過去嗎
You want this to go away?
-是的        -好  拿出你的錢包
- Yes.              - Okay, pull out your wallet.
-來吧  拿出來             -你就是這么訛人的嗎
- Come on, get it out.             - Do you shake down everybody like this?
不  只對小部分特殊人士管用
No, only the special few.
瞧瞧這  200塊怎么樣  這事鬧大了  那就250塊吧
What is this? Two hundred seem fair? You know what? This is a big deal. Let's go $250.
-你是街頭賣藝的搶劫犯             -啊，我就是呀
- You're a stick-up artist.                       - Yeah. Of course.
好了  睡吧
Okay, and sleep!
當我再打響指時  你會忘記剛才的一切
Now, when I snap my fingers, you won't remember any of this.
而你  華倫·貝蒂
And you, Warren Beatty,
以後每次你見到甚至想到詹尼特  腦中都會浮現出我裸體的樣子
every time you see or even think of Janet, you're gonna picture me naked.
-那可沒甚麼好看           -這是一定的
- And that's not a pretty sight.                  - Yeah.
現在  你醒了
And... You're wide awake!
我們盡力了
Well, we did the best we could,
但有些人就是沒辦法被催眠
but some people just aren't to be hypnotized.
-我做錯了嗎            -來吧  親愛的
- I did it wrong?                      - Come on, Honey Bee.
沒有  你做得很好
Oh, no, you did it fine.
我們去吃晚飯吧
Let me buy you dinner.
照顧好她
Look after her.
不過得先找ATM機取錢
Just have to hit an ATM first.
紐約   星期三
女士們先生們  我是下一任大魔術師
Ladies and gentlemen, I am the next great magician,
識破我魔術的人將得到100塊獎勵
and I will give $100 to anyone who can tell me how this trick is done.
這是一把的普通勺子
I have an ordinary spoon from Mel's Deli,
就從布魯克林的梅爾斯德裡餐廳拿來的
right here in Brooklyn.
看看
Check it out.
現在請大家集中注意力
Now, everyone please pay very, very close attention.
我要用意念來彎曲這把勺子
Because I'm about to bend this spoon with my mind.
謝謝  謝謝  傳下去吧
Thank you. Thank you. Pass that around.
-這是甚麼                  -你在干甚麼
- What's this?                               - What are you doing, man?
快看  這有把勺子和一根勺柄
Look at this! Looks like we got a spoon and a stem.
我還會別的魔術
I've got other tricks.
先把那100塊給我
Or you could give me my 100 bucks.
你說了你會給的
You said you would.
錢包不錯嘛
Nice wallet.
好眼力  先生
You have a very good eye, sir.
謝謝
Thanks.
我的錢包
Wallet.
我的錢包  我的手表
My wallet. My watch!
攔住那家伙
Stop that guy!
攔住那個穿皮夾克的人
Stop that guy in the leather jacket!
他拿了我的錢包
He's got my wallet!
洛杉磯   星期四
洛杉磯
Okay, Los Angeles,
準備好欣賞壓軸大戲了嗎
are we ready to end this thing?
沒錯
Yeah!
當那計時器歸零
When that timer hits zero,
這裝滿食人魚的箱子
a tank full of flesh-eating piranhas
將會落下
will fall from above.
我得被銬住  對嗎  女孩們
A lady has to have handcuffs. Right, girls?
一  二  三
One, two, three!
救命  快停下
Help! Stop it!
她是真出不來了
She's serious! She can't get out!
去找人幫忙
Go get some help!
來幫忙啊  伙計
Help, dude!
都站一邊去  讓開  讓開
Get out of the way! Move! Move!
得了吧  動動腦子
Come on! This is bullshit!
設計這魔術的人就是個變態
Whoever thought of this is a sick sadist!
我是你最忠實的粉絲
I am your biggest fan.
看得出來  親我都跟刨地似的
I could tell by the way you're attacking my face right now.
關上門  這公寓真差勁
Close the door. Bad apartment building.
-魔術師  過來                  -好的
- Magician, come here.                             - Okay.
-等等                  -怎么了
- Wait, wait.                        - What? What?
你是怎么做到的
How did you do that...
大樓上的方片七嗎
The seven of diamonds on the side of the tower?
-是的                  -那是業內機密
- Yes.                 - That's a trade secret.
我給你個提示  我賄賂了大樓的電工
I'll give you a hint. It involved bribing the tower electrician.
多少錢
How much?
50塊
50 bucks.
-但是那真難                  -謝謝你
- But it's so hard.                                 - Oh, thank you.
那張牌只能是方片七嗎
Is it always a seven?
我可以用52種方式來變那個魔術
I could do that trick 52 different ways.
你能在我身上變52種魔術嗎
Can you do 52 different tricks on me?
我會盡力的
I'll see what I can do.
魔術師
Magic man!
我喜歡你的洗發水味
I love your shampoo.
-等等                  -怎么了
- Hold up.                              - What?
你先走吧
You need to leave.
開甚麼玩笑
Are you kidding me?
天啊  丟死人了
Oh, my God, this is so embarrassing.
原來你是這種人
Is this what you do?
用下三濫的把戲欺騙良家婦女嗎
Some kind of sick trick you do to women?
3月29號   下午4點44分
東伊凡街45號   紐約
"東伊凡街45號"
"45 East Evan Street."
別擔心  我會打給你的
Don't worry about it. I'll call you.
你都沒有我的號碼
You don't have my number.
我是魔術師  我會弄到的  晚安
I'm magic. I'll find it. Have a good night.
你就是個混蛋
You are such an asshole.
3月29號    下午4點44分
東伊凡街45號   紐約
亨莉
Henley.
丹尼  你好
Danny? Hey.
你也收到了一張卡對吧
You got a card, huh?
不不  挺好的  恭喜你
No,no,no, it's good for you. Congratulations.
我打算這么做
All right, so here's what I'm gonna do,
我要進去  探探路
I'm gonna go inside. I'm gonna scope the place out.
你在外面等著  我會回來接你的
You wait out here. I will come back and get you, okay?
別進來
Do not come in.
丹尼  我已經不是你的助手了
Hey, Danny! I'm not your assistant anymore.
發型不錯嘛
Nice hair.
你最近都在忙甚麼呢
So, actually, what have you been up to?
你心知肚明  丹尼
I think you know exactly what I've been up to, Danny.
我知道你一直在匿名關注我的網站
I saw all your anonymous posting on my website.
你還有個網站  不錯嘛
You have a website. That's good.
挺不錯  多做宣傳
Good for you. Get the word out.
很明顯被選中的人不止一個
So apparently none of us was the only one chosen.
那就讓我來打開話匣子吧
Let me be the first one to kick my ego to the curb.
請讓一下
Yeah. Excuse me.
-門鎖了                  -是嗎  我看看
- Door's locked.                         - Is it? I'll check.
你  等等  別告訴我
You. Now, hold it, don't tell me.
海倫嗎  不是
Helen? No, no.
亨莉
Henley.
咖啡杯上寫著呢
It's on your coffee cup.
多謝拆臺
Thanks for keeping me honest.
那不是讀心術
That wasn't mentalism, by the way.
只是一種觀察
It was just an observation.
再觀察一下  你真漂亮
Second observation, you are beautiful.
謝謝
Thank you.
挺好  不錯  說得很好  很妙
That's good. That's very nice. Very well-polished. Nice bit.
我是J·丹尼爾·阿特拉斯  很高興見到你
J. Daniel Atlas. Nice to meet you.
很好  我知道你是誰  我只想說
Very nice. I know who you are and I just want to say that
我們可沒閑工夫讓你施展你的讀心術
I'm not interested in you doing your mentalism thing on us.
而且現在那位邀請我們的
Especially when we don't know
神秘人的意圖還尚不明了
who brought us here or even if it's real.
等等  我感覺到  你的控制欲異常強烈
Hold on, I'm sensing... I'm sensing you are a control freak.
很抱歉  我們以前見過面嗎
I'm sorry, have we met before?
不用讀心術也看得出來
It doesn't take a mentalist to figure that out.
你就一控制癖
You are a control freak.
我就當這是表揚了
Well, I take that as a compliment.
只有他才會把這當做是褒獎
Only he would take it as a compliment.
多好  你看她又表揚我
Okay, great. Good. Another compliment.
這就是你們沒繼續在一起的原因了
Okay. So that's why you're no longer a couple.
在一起  不不
A couple? No, no.
我們從沒在一起過
We were never a couple.
他以前經常把我鋸成兩半
He used to saw me in half.
她是個很棒的助手
She was a very good assistant.
但是對他來說我太胖了
But I was too fat for Danny.
不  我那次這么說是因為那暗門
No. I said that one time because of the trap door.
-有固定規格的                  -你做得這么小
- There were specs.                                   - You built it this size.
沒有人能擠進去  沒有人
No one could fit through there. No one.
麗貝卡可以
Rebecca fit through.
麗貝卡很多年都擠得進去
Rebecca fit for years.
你知道要維持身材
Do you know how hard it is
穿下那么小的服裝有多難嗎
to stay in those tiny little costumes?
不知道  我才是魔術的主角
No. I'm the main attraction.
就是說他從沒讓你感到自己很出眾嗎
Okay. So he never made you feel special.
相信我  你應該對自己的才華多些信心
And, trust me, you deserve to be made to feel special.
故事講得不錯
That's a really nice story.
祝你倆搭檔愉快
Hope you guys enjoy each other's company.
不是吧
No way.
J·丹尼爾·阿特拉斯
J. Daniel Atlas?
我看過你所有的表演
Dude, I've seen everything that you have ever done.
你就像個
You're like...
我很崇拜你  說真的
I idolize you. Seriously.
的確是我的死忠  見到你真好
From a true fan. It's so nice to meet you.
我叫杰克
I'm Jack, by the way.
問一下  你也得到卡片了嗎
Question. Did you get one of these?
以下都是塔羅牌裡的角色
有  死神
Yeah. Death.
女祭司
The High Priestess.
我的是戀人
I'm the Lover.
三分鐘
Three minutes.
隱士
Hermit.
我們在  我們在等人嗎
So, what are we... Are we waiting for someone?
-為甚麼我們                  -門鎖了
- Why are we just...                             - The door's locked.
不  沒有打不開的鎖
Oh, no, nothing's ever locked.
這是甚麼地方
What is this place?
我還以為我的公寓算臟的呢
Wow. Thought my apartment was nasty.
裡面好冷啊
Man, it's freezing in here.
那是甚麼
What's that?
我不知道
I don't know.
上面寫了甚麼
What's it say?
"看不見他"
"Now you don't."
出自迪斯尼電影《Now You See Him, Now You Don't》
"玫瑰不因其名而香"
"A rose by any other name..."
伙計們  這是怎么一回事
Guys, what's happening?
快看
Look at that.
有氣體溢出來了
It's gas!
放心  只是干冰而已
Relax. Just dry ice.
真酷
Cool.
你們覺得這是怎么一回事
Wait. What do you think this is all about?
等等  等等
Hang on. Hang on.
啥都沒想到
I got nothin'.
多謝你耽誤時間
Okay. Thank you. Thank you for the delay.
我只是給大家幾秒思考的空間
I'm just trying to create the space for wisdom.
搞得自己像菩薩一樣
Okay, so you're like Buddha,
只是沒那么靈光罷了
if he wasn't so enlightened.
那你就像耶穌
And you're like Jesus,
自大狂妄  用虛假的把戲誆騙世人
if he was arrogant and all of his miracles were fake.
夠了  公共場合就別打情罵俏了
Okay, lovebirds, get a room.
丹尼  說實話  這是你干的嗎
Danny, be honest. Did you do this?
不是  等等  是你干的嗎
No. Wait, did you?
我倒想
I Wish.
為甚麼沒有人問是不是我干的
Why didn't anyone ask me if I did it?
這下好了
Oh, great.
屋子裡沒通電
Electricity is out.
是嗎  試試看
Well, let's check.
藍圖
Blueprints.
好奇妙
They're incredible.
你們覺得這是誰做的
Who do you think did this?
不知道  但我很想見見他們
I don't know, but I really want to meet them.
是一場演出
It's a show.
驚 天 魔 盜 團
拉斯維加斯
一年之後
梅利特·麥金尼
Merritt McKinney,
丹尼爾·阿特拉斯
Daniel Atlas,
亨莉·裡維斯
Henley Reeves,
杰克·瓦爾德
Jack Wilder.
亞瑟·特萊斯勒攜手米高梅酒店榮譽呈現
Arthur Tressler and the MGM Grand proudly presents,
天啟四騎士
The Four Horsemen.
謝謝
Thank you.
今晚  我們將要
Tonight we would like to try something
做些與眾不同的嘗試
that will, well, set us a bit apart.
我們的閉幕演出
For our final trick,
將會是這拉斯維加斯舞臺上
we're gonna do something never before
甚至任何舞臺上
seen on a Las Vegas stage.
都前所未見的
Or any stage for that matter.
女士們先生們
Ladies and gentlemen,
今晚  我們要搶銀行
tonight, we are going to rob a bank.
大家對犯罪都很激動啊
That's a lot of excitement for a crime.
我很激動  你們呢
I'm getting excited. What about you, people?
一  二  三
One, two, three!
對不起  先生  在演出期間
Sorry, sir. There's absolutely no recording allowed
嚴禁錄像
during the performance.
好的  好的  沒問題
Oh, yeah, yeah, sure, of course.
我把它收起來
Let me just put this away.
抱歉  我得將其沒收
Actually, I need to take that.
演出結束後再還給您
After the show, I can come and give it back to you.
好吧
Okay.
好的  好的
Okay, okay.
現在請大家安靜下來
Now, please, please, settle down.
我們搶哪家銀行呢
Now who here has a bank they would like us to rob?
看來很多人都和銀行有血海深仇啊
That's a lot of people with a vendetta.
那我們就隨機挑選一個
So we'll choose one at random then.
我的搭檔們會確保挑選是隨機的  對吧
My associates will make sure it's random. Right?
貓王  幫個忙  伙計
Elvis, help me out, bud.
非常感謝
Thank you very much.
杰克的碗裡是寫著區域號的乒乓球
In Jack's bowl are ping pong balls with section numbers.
杰克  扔給我一個區域號吧
Jack, could you hand me a section number?
謝謝  是B區
Thank you. We are looking at Section B.
B區在哪裡
Where is Section B?
好的  在那
Okay. There.
會是你們中的一員  準備好
It's gonna be one of you guys. Get ready.
為甚麼大家都很高興
I don't know why everybody's happy.
選到的是他們
It's only them.
梅利特  請選個座排號吧
Merritt, can I get a row, please?
謝謝你  梅利特
Thank you, Merritt.
是第五排
We are looking at row number 5.
在哪
Where is that?
亨莉  隨機選個座位號好嗎
And Henley, could I please have a random seat number?
幸運數13號
Oh. Lucky number 13.
B區5排13號  你在哪
B-5-13. Where are you?
先生  請起立  是那位  你好
Sir, please, stand up. There you are. Hi.
請你確認一下
Could you just confirm for me
你的座位號是B區5排13號對嗎
that this is, in fact, your seat? B-5-13.
對
Yes.
非常好  現在請你告訴大家
Okay. Wonderful. Now, could you please tell us
你的名字和你光顧的銀行
your name and the name of your bank?
我叫艾蒂安·馮希爾
Well, my name is Etienne Forcier.
銀行是巴黎信貸共和銀行
And my bank, it's Credit Republicain de Paris.
法國的  好吧
French. Okay.
我們本希望找個本地的
We were hoping for something a little more local,
沒甚麼安保的小銀行
a kind of mom-and-pop credit union with no security.
不過也可以  說到做到
But that's fine. A promise is a promise.
請你到臺上來
Could you please come up to the stage
我們要搶你的銀行
and we'll rob your bank.
趁他上臺的這段時間我要說
And while he does that,
今晚來的一個人
there is someone here tonight
如果沒有他的話
without whom we would just be
我們就只是四個名不見經傳的魔術師
four magicians working the circuit,
努力想要登上今天這個舞臺
trying to get, well, actually, trying to get here.
他旗下管理著諸多公司
You probably know this man,
即使不是其中員工你也沒準認識他
if not from one of the many, many companies he puts his name on.
他就是我們的朋友  我們的贊助人
He is our friend. He is our benefactor.
亞瑟·特萊斯勒先生
Mr. Arthur Tressler.
請站起來  亞瑟  請起
Please, stand up, Art. Please, stand up.
眾人中唯一一個
The only man here with
有女王手機號的人
the Queen's cell phone number.
請不要坐下  亞瑟
Actually, please, stay standing, Art.
我想說
I want to say that
當我們剛找到特萊斯勒先生的時候
when we came to Mr. Tressler,
我們保證過  作為一個團隊
we promised that, as a unit, we could become
我們會成為魔術史上的翹楚
the biggest name in magic.
我們想說  謝謝您
So we wanted to say, "Thank you."
順便說一下  亞瑟  您可以看到
And by the way, Art, you notice on the sign out front,
我們把你的名字寫在了招牌的最頂端
we made sure we put your name on top.
如果你能做到
If you turn out to be as good
如你想象的那樣好  親愛的
as you think you are, dear girl,
我的名字就不重要了
that won't be necessary much longer.
我們還沒完成壓軸大戲
We haven't done our closer yet.
不如您先來看看
Why don't you watch it
然後自己決定
and then you can decide for yourself.
女士們先生們  亞瑟·特萊斯勒
Ladies and gentlemen, Arthur Tressler!
謝謝你  再一次
Thank you. And, of course, once again,
目光回到魔力大師  梅利特·麥金尼
the Cardinal of Clairvoyance, Merritt McKinney.
艾蒂安  現在杰克拿到舞臺上來的
Etienne, what Jack is bringing to the stage now,
在魔術界稱為幻行頭盔
is what we in the magic world call a teleportation helmet.
你得帶上它  它會使你
You will need to wear this, as it will allow you
真正穿梭時空
to literally fold through space and time
去到銀行所在的
to your bank in the
第八區嗎
8th?
-第九區                  -是的
- 9th arrondissement.                 - Yeah.
一旦你到那
Now, once you are there,
我們能夠通過頭盔對話
we will be able to speak with you through this helmet.
如果
Now if...
天啊  很漂亮
Oh, my God, that's beautiful.
更有型更有魅力了
It has the added attraction of being very stylish.
是時候讓法國人  從美國學學時尚了
It's about time the French learned from America on that subject.
多漂亮的頭飾啊
Is that a beautiful piece of headgear?
-謝謝  謝謝                  -的確是
- Thank you. Thank you...                               - it is.
謝謝  非常感謝
Thank you. Thank you very much.
在你出發之前
But before you go anywhere,
請你挑一張牌  任意一張
could you please, pick a card, any card.
別挑那張
Not that card.
不  這是個美式笑話  那張也行
No, that's an old American joke. You can take that one.
好的  這張嗎
Okay. This one?
給B區的觀眾們看  別讓我們看到
Show it to your friends in Section B. But not to us.
非常好  現在請你在牌上簽名
Okay, great. Now if you could just sign your name there.
-好的                  -可以的話  請用英語
- Yes.                                              - In English, if possible.
-很好                  -謝謝
- That's good.                             - Thanks.
放進你的口袋
Put it in your pocket.
現在還差一個小細節
And now for one tiny detail.
艾蒂安  現在請走進這個精妙的裝置中
Now, Etienne, let's step into this cockamamie contraption.
我得退出來  祝你好運
And I'll step off of it. Bonne chance.
現在拉斯維加斯時間是晚上11點50分
It's 11:50 p.m. Here in Vegas.
也就是巴黎的早上8點50分
And 8:50 a.m. In Paris.
你的銀行還有不到10分鐘就開門了
Your bank opens in less than 10 minutes.
一
One,
二
two,
三
Three.
怎么回事
What the fuck?
-艾蒂安                  -艾蒂安
- Etienne?                                      - Etienne?
計劃中不是這樣的吧  是嗎
It wasn't supposed to happen like that, was it?
艾蒂安
Etienne?
我還挺喜歡那個法國佬的
I liked that little French guy.
他哪去了
Where did he go?
巴黎   同一時間
等等  他在那
Wait, there he is.
不  不  不  請安靜
No, no, no, no, please, please, please.
我是丹尼爾·阿特拉斯  你能聽見嗎
This is Daniel Atlas. Can you hear me?
艾蒂安  你沒事吧
Etienne? Are you okay?
沒事
Yes.
很好  你看見了甚麼
Perfect. What do you see in there?
錢
Money.
是真的嗎
Is this real?
是的  看起來大概有三百萬歐元
Yes. Looks like three million or so Euros' worth.
你接下來要做的是
Okay, now, here's what we're gonna need you to do.
把那張簽過名的紙牌
I want you to take the card that you signed
從口袋裡拿出來
out of your pocket.
還有今晚演出的門票存根
And I want you to take the ticket stub
也拿出來
from tonight's show
我要你把它們
and I want you to put it right there
放在錢的正中間
in the middle of the money.
現在  扔下去
Now drop it.
信貸共和
在你頭盔的一側  有一個按鈕
Now, on the side of your helmet you should feel a button.
先不要按
Don't press it just yet.
那按鈕會啟動一個
That button activates an air duct
連接巴黎和拉斯維加斯的通風管
that connects Paris to Las Vegas.
好  很好  現在按下去
Okay, good. Now you can press it.
好的  艾蒂安  請站穩
All right, now, Etienne, hold on tight.
你會感覺要被吸走
You might feel a bit of a vacuum.
等一下
Wait a second.
該死
Ah merde!
謝謝你  艾蒂安  謝謝大家
Thank you, Etienne. Thank you, everyone!
我們是天啟四騎士
We are The Four Horsemen.
晚安
And good night!
Good night!
等等
Hold up here.
迪倫·羅茲
Dylan Rhodes.
甚麼  我聽錯了吧
What? I don't think I heard you correctly.
你是說魔術師
Did you say magicians?
是的  迪倫  魔術師
Yeah, Dylan, magicians.
你現在在哪
Where are you now?
我在阿利亞酒店  正要上去抓他們
I'm at Aria. I'm heading up there to grab 'em now.
聯邦調查局  舉起手來
FBI! Hands where I can see them.
上  抓住他們
Let's go. Get 'em up. Come on.
Let's go. Get 'em up.
放下書
Put the book down.
好吧  被你抓到了
Okay. You got me.
-不許動  舉起手來                  -天啊
- Freeze! Hands in the air!                                   - Oh, my!
誰來幫我們拿一下行李箱
Do one of you guys mind giving us a hand with our bags?
跟我走
Let's go.
老大  你一定是開玩笑呢
Boss, please tell me this is a joke.
威利·米爾斯剛指認了寶利·阿塔納西奧
I just got Willy Mears to finger Paulie Attanasio.
我穩住手頭的案子
I'm a month, two tops,
才一個月  最多兩個月
away from blowing this whole thing open.
這案子讓特克森辦吧
Get Turkelson.
他在大西洋城
He's in Atlantic City.
那科恩呢  看看他
What about Cowan? Look at him.
瞧他那成天坐著無所事事的樣兒
He's just sitting there on his ass.
真好笑  羅茲
Hilarious, Rhodes.
我愛你
I love you.
混蛋
Asshole.
我沒時間管這堆破爛魔術
I don't have time for this magic crap.
這堆破爛剛從巴黎的一家銀行
This crap just pulled three million Euro
偷了三百萬歐元
out of a Parisian bank.
-他們偷了這么多                  -是的
- That's how much they got?                            - Yeah.
實際上是三百二十萬
Actually, 3.2.
她是誰
Who is she?
你是誰
Who are you?
國際刑警組織的艾爾瑪·德雷
Alma Dray from Interpol.
我將和你一起調查
I'll be working the investigation with you.
你沒看玩笑吧
You gotta be kidding me.
讓我去抓大衛·科波菲爾和朋友們
It's bad enough they got me chasing down
大衛·科波菲爾：著名魔術師
就夠糟糕的了
David Copperfield and Friends.
現在還有國際刑警拖後腿  無意冒犯
Now I'm being saddled with, no offense, with Interpol?
我也很期待我們的合作  羅茲特工
I look forward to working with you, too, Agent Rhodes.
抱歉  我不需要你的幫助  明白嗎
I'm sorry. I don't think I'm gonna need your help on this. Okay?
那個法國人在哪
Where's the French guy?
我已經和他談過了
I already spoke to him.
你談過了  你搶先和我的證人談過了
Oh, you did? You spoke to my witness before me?
你的證人  我還以為你不想接這案子
Your witness? I thought you didn't want the case.
再說  他也沒有審問價值了
Besides, he's useless.
是嗎  為甚麼
Oh, really? Why is that?
因為他相信他們的魔術是真的
Because he believes their magic was real.
他相信魔術是真的
Oh, he believes the magic was real?
你說的對  沒準他是沒甚麼用了
You're right, he probably is useless.
國際刑警不介意我再和他談談吧
Is it okay with Interpol if we talk to him, too?
謝謝
Thank you.
我從沒做過偷雞摸狗的事  明白嗎
I have never stolen a thing in my life, okay?
我想把錢還回去  但他們不收
I tried to give the money back, but they won't take it.
好吧  好吧  姑且說你搶了銀行
Okay, okay, okay, let's just say you robbed a bank.
-搶了                  -很好  非常好  你搶了
- I did.                                                  - Fine. Fantastic. You did.
因為我剛接手  你解釋一下
But since I'm new to this, can you explain to me
你是怎么在三秒鐘內
how you went from Las Vegas
從拉斯維加斯跑到巴黎的
to Paris in three seconds?
因為有幻行頭盔
With the teleportation helmet.
好吧  這到底怎么回事
Okay, what the hell is going on here?
他在演出時被催眠了
He was hypnotized during the show.
我說過  他沒甚麼審問價值了
I told you, he's useless.
等我處理完其他混蛋
Okay, I'll deal with you when I'm done
在找你算賬
with this other bullshit.
在演出時  有一半的觀眾都被催眠了
During the show, half the audience was hypnotized
以為他們在交響樂團
to believe they were in the Philharmonic.
我猜"混蛋"是觸發詞
I guess that "Bullshit" Was the trigger word.
聽著  艾蒂安  快下來
Okay. Hey, hey. Ecoutez. Etienne, come on down from there.
你不是在交響樂團
You're not in the Philharmonic.
-法語的"停下"怎么說                  -停下
- How do you say "Stop" In French?                                - Stop.
讓他停下來
Tell him to stop.
沒辦法  你得讓他奏完這個樂章
No, I can't. You just have to let him finish his movement.
好吧  我得休息一下
Okay, I need a time-out.
這屋子裡法國人太多了
Too many French people in one room.
羅茲特工
Agent Rhodes!
我受命而來  要調查出個結果
I'm ordered by my bosses to provide a report.
在結案之前
And until we have one,
不論如何  我都會在這待著
I'm here, like it or not.
要么合作
So we can work together,
要么就跟在我後面
or you can continue to follow behind
再問一遍我問過的問題
asking the same exact questions I'm asking.
你來決定
It's up to you.
我還沒說完呢
I'm not finished.
我累了一天  又飛了12個小時
I just flew 12 hours, after what was already a long day.
還沒調整好時差
And I do not handle jet lag well.
想和我比脾氣暴躁
So if you want to see who can be grumpier,
我敢保證  你可差遠了
I promise you, you will lose.
好吧  這幾個白癡中
Fine. So which one of these idiots
你想先談哪個
do you want to talk to first?
他嗎
Him?
迪倫  事先聲明
Dylan, for the record,
讀心術從來沒被證實過
mentalism has never actually been proven to be accurate.
好的
Okay.
也就是說  這不是一門科學
That is to say, that it's not a science.
最多就是一種消遣
It's more for entertainment.
好的
All right.
所以不要相信他所說的任何話
Just don't believe everything the guy says. That's all.
請代我向你外面的同事
Please convey my deepest apologies
表達誠摯的歉意
to your colleague out there.
對變裝星期二的事  我感到抱歉
I'm really sorry about this whole Tranny Tuesday thing.
我太過火了
I was out of line.
變裝星期二
Tranny Tuesday?
是他和妻子的小約定
Well, it's an arrangement he and his wife have.
如果你相信富勒特工說的都是實話
Or might not have, if you believe
就當我沒提
everything Agent Fuller is saying to be correct.
不過嘛  聯邦調查局裡有
But isn't there a proud tradition
大男人穿裙子這樣的光榮傳統嗎
in the FBI of men wearing dresses?
別害羞  富勒特工  別害羞
No shame, Agent Fuller. No shame.
開個玩笑罷了
I'm just having fun.
這張是你的牌嗎  不是
Was this your card? No.
看  我就知道你不是選紅桃皇后那種女士
See, I knew you weren't a queen of hearts lady,
我很欣賞你這點
and I respect that.
要是沒被困在這兒  我能表演得更好
The trick usually works better when I'm not strapped in here,
不過我對你們的政策表示理解
but I understand protocol.
好了  好了
Okay, okay.
如果不是你做的
So, if you had nothing to do with it,
那魔術牌怎么會出現在金庫
then how did the playing card get into the vault?
對了  那就是所謂的
Oh, yes. That would be...
現今的孩子都怎么稱呼來著
What do the kids call it these days?
沒錯  想起來了  魔法
Oh, yes, that's right. Magic.
快點回答問題  大天才
Just answer the question, okay, smartass.
好的  抱歉  抱歉  抱歉
All right. Sorry, sorry, sorry.
這罐送你了  別給他喝
You can keep that. Don't share it with him.
這上面說你是個讀心者
It says here you are a mentalist.
讀心術到底是怎么進行的
What exactly is mentalism?
大部分是靠戲法  也用一些科學
Tricks, mostly. Some science.
可以說是對對象的一種針對性猜測吧
Targeted guessing might be a most apt description.
還有運用我的直覺和偶爾
Along with some intuition and the occasional...
腦中閃過的靈光
voices in my head.
據說你一度非常出名
Says here you were fairly famous at one point.
甚至能通過電話進行催眠
You can even hypnotize people over the phone.
有幾年還在全美做大型巡回演出
Some big tours around the U.S for a few years.
出過兩個電視專題節目
Two TV specials.
光輝歲月啊
Glory days.
後來你的哥哥兼經紀人
Then your brother/manager
帶著你辛苦掙來的錢一起消失了
disappeared with all your hard-earned money.
你功課做得很足啊
Did your research, did you?
稅務稽核署  欠繳稅款
IRS audit. Back taxes.
重返舞臺的過程一定不容易吧
You've had a long hard slog back into the limelight,
是嗎  麥金尼先生
haven't you, Mr. McKinney?
沒錯  的確是這樣
Yes, indeed, it has.
也多謝你揭我傷疤
And I do appreciate that trip down Memory Lane.
就我所知  當那個巴黎男
As far as I understand it, when the man from Paris
戴上魔法頭盔
put on the magical helmet...
聽好
Listen to me.
就算不是你搶的銀行  你也是知情者
If you didn't rob that bank, then you knew about it.
那么你就是同謀
Which makes you an accomplice.
所以如果你今天想走出這裡  我建議你
So if you wanna walk out of here today, I'd suggest you start...
現在你給我聽好  除非你覺得
Now you listen to me, unless you think
內華達州有哪個地方檢察官
there's a D.A. in the state of Nevada
會愿意把這個案子提交給陪審團
who'd be willing to make sense of this to a jury,
不然最後還是得放我們回去準備演出
then we have a show to perform.
至于你  羅茲探員
And you, Agent Rhodes,
得回去重新理理思路了
have a drawing board to get back to.
這是你倆第一次約會嗎
Is this your first date?
甚麼
What?
不  我的意思是  很明顯
No, I mean, obviously,
你們倆根本不熟  甚至完全不了解對方
you guys don't know each other well, if at all.
但這屋裡卻有一種微妙的緊張感
But, like, there is a palpable tension in this room.
在參與進來之前
And before you get involved,
你就該考慮到她藏著很多秘密
you should consider the fact that she has a lot of big secrets.
其中之一就是
And I know the first one is that
這是你第一次外勤任務  是嗎
this is your first time off the desk. Isn't it?
你本該自己跟他說的
You should have said something to him.
通過這種方式知道很奇怪吧
This is a weird way for you to find out.
你這是明擺著想被拘捕  知道嗎
You are literally begging to be arrested. You know that?
前提是你真會那么做  但是你不會
If it means you would actually do it, then, yeah. But you won't.
因為如果你那么做了  那就意味著你
Because if you did, it means that you,
還有聯邦調查局
and the FBI,
以及你的國際刑警朋友
and your friends at Interpol,
一直以來都相信  魔術的真實性
actually believe, at an institutional level, in magic.
一定會讓媒體嘩然的
The press would have a field day.
至于我們  會變得比現在還出名
And we'd be even more famous than we already are.
而你們只會被看成一群白癡
And you guys would look like idiots
雖然已經是了
even more then you already are.
不  沒說你  說的是他
Well, no, not you. But him. Right?
用我們的行話說就是  你們會
You have, what we in the business, like to call,
沒有一點勝算
"Nothing up your sleeve."
你明白的
And you know it.
別讓他迷上你然後又甩了他
Don't draw him in and then dump him
因為遺棄對他來說是個大陰影
because abandonment is a big "Area" For him.
媽媽
Mommy?
是爸爸
Daddy.
你跟爸爸有很大的問題
You have big daddy issues.
-行了  夠了                  -我告訴你
- Okay, that's enough.                      - I'll tell you what.
你去找心理醫生
Your average therapist
平均花費要一次200到300塊
is gonna charge you $200-$300 for this sesh.
找我的話  只要10塊
Me? I'll take a tenner.
如果你覺得不差這點兒錢
Okay, later, if you're feeling magnanimous,
我還是只收10塊
I'll still take a tenner.
想知道你那張椅子之前都有誰坐過嗎
You wanna know who sat in that chair before you?
黑手黨老大  謀殺犯  還有小偷
Mob bosses, murderers, and thieves.
你知道誰把他們抓進來的嗎
And you know who put them there?
現在坐在你面前的這個人
The guy who's sitting in this chair.
所以我警告你  我有足夠的耐心
So I warn you, I can maintain my resolve much longer
等到你無法繼續那些自鳴得意的騙術
than you can maintain that phony arrogance.
一旦你那引以為豪的表情露出
And the instant that you even show
哪怕是一丁點破綻
the slightest crack in that smug facade,
我都會窮追不舍的
I'll be there.
我會時刻跟著你  就像
I will be all over you like...
小鳥依人一樣嗎
Like white on rice?
抱歉  那么說不對
Sorry. That's unfair.
提醒你一句
Let me warn you.
我希望你跟緊我們
I want you to follow.
因為不管你以為自己知道些甚麼
Because no matter what you think you might know,
我們永遠會比你走得更快一步
we will always be one step,
三步  甚至七步
three steps, seven steps ahead of you.
當你以為把我們抓個正著的時候
And just when you think you're catching up,
其實我們已經在你身後了
that's when we'll be right behind you.
不管是甚麼時候
And at no time will you be anywhere other than
你只會被我牽著鼻子走
exactly where I want you to be.
所以盡管靠近點  放馬過來
So come close. Get all over me,
因為你覺得自己越接近
because the closer you think you are,
能看到的事實越少
the less you'll actually see.
我一定會抓住你
I'm gonna nail you...
那瓶蘇打是不是有甚麼問題啊  小姐
Something wrong with that soda, Miss?
糟糕
Oh! Shit!
魔術師第一守則
First rule of magic.
永遠做房間裡最聰明的一個
Always be the smartest guy in the room.
老大  現在甚麼情況
Boss, what are we doing?
就這么放他們走
We're letting them go?
他們都承認還會再這么做了
They all but admitted they're gonna do it again.
半個小時前  你還對他們毫不在意
About a half an hour ago, you didn't give a damn about them.
-現在怎么變了                  -眼見為實
- What changed?                                               - I met them.
大伙兒
Hey. Guys.
我去查過觀眾的情況了
Hey, I ran a check on the audience.
大部分都是用來充人數的
Most of it was just filler.
被特萊斯勒拉進去提高上座率
People that Tressler dragged in to pack the room.
但你猜是誰坐在那兒
But guess who was sitting there in the back,
把整個過程拍下來了
filming the whole damn thing?
不知道
I don't know.
撒迪厄斯·布雷德利
Thaddeus Bradley.
撒迪厄斯·布雷德利  電視上
Thaddeus Bradley, the guy from TV
賣DVD和做節目的那個
with the DVDs and shows?
不認識
No.
好吧  他專門給魔術做揭秘
Okay, well, he debunks magicians.
他揭發魔術師  給你演示他們的戲法
He exposes them. He shows you how to do their tricks.
馬上電話聯系他
Get him on the phone.
打過了  約了45分鐘後跟你一起吃飯
I did. You're having lunch with him in 45.
很好
Good.
布雷德利先生最初也是個魔術師
Mr. Bradley started as a magician.
-當時做的挺成功                  -真的嗎
- He was actually quite good.                            - Really?
-首屈一指                  -我猜也是
- One of the best.                               - You don't say.
看穿表象的偉大天才
"The greatest genius is in seeing through the illusion."
真是個熱愛工作的男人
That's a man who loves his work.
你覺得我能不能用一杯紅酒引起你的興趣
You sure I can't interest you in a glass of wine?
不不不  不用了
No, no, no.
謝謝你  先生  我們還在工作
No, thank you, sir. We're working.
我倒想來一杯
I will take one.
真是不可思議  太棒了
That's incredible. That's amazing.
紅色素  藏在手心裡
Red dye, palmed.
紅酒被認為是耶穌的鮮血
耶穌就是這么玩的嗎
Is that how Jesus did it?
真是太不可思議了
That's incredible.
抱歉  我能先耽誤你一分鐘嗎
I'm sorry. Can I just take a minute here?
你以前可是個偉大的魔術師
You were one of the great magicians.
為甚麼不干了呢
Why did you stop?
你知道過去五年間有多少人觀看了
Do you know how many people went to see magic performed live
現場魔術表演嗎
in the last half decade?
大約160萬
About 1.6 million.
你又知道同樣時間我賣了多少DVD嗎
You know how many DVDs I sold in the same period?
500萬
Five million.
懂了  所以是因為金錢利益
Right, so it's about the money.
掙這些錢只是因為
Well, the money is only there
想要獲知真相的人遠比
because the need to know is greater than
樂意被蒙在鼓裡的人多
the desire to be fooled.
跟你一樣  我痛恨
Like you, I detest those
那些靠欺詐無知大眾為生的人
who prey upon the gullibility of the masses.
恕我直言
With all due respect,
這樣做不會對魔術這個行業產生影響嗎
isn't there a cost, though, to this game?
代價
Cost?
不清楚  比如事業
I don't know. Careers.
生命
Lives.
我猜你指的是萊昂納爾·施萊克
I assume you're referring to Lionel Shrike.
不好意思  誰
I'm sorry, who?
萊昂納爾·施萊克
Lionel Shrike.
30年前淹死在哈德遜河的
A middling magician who drowned
一個二流魔術師
in the Hudson River 30 years ago.
布雷德利先生第一次做專題節目
On Mr. Bradley's first special,
他破解了施萊克的所有戲法
he revealed all of Shrike's tricks.
第二年  施萊克想要東山再起
The next year, Shrike tried to stage a comeback.
他被關進一個保險箱
He was shackled inside a safe,
然後丟進了河裡
and dropped into the river.
但他再也沒有浮上水面
But he never resurfaced.
你意思是說他死了
You mean he died?
不是我害死他的
I didn't kill him.
是他害死了自己
He killed himself
他挑戰了自己還不能運用自如的魔術
trying to do something he wasn't prepared to handle.
你應該明白這是場游戲了吧
You do realize this is a game?
相信我  這絕不是場游戲
Believe me, it's not a game.
就是場游戲
It is a game.
你本身就是游戲  被人玩弄于股掌
You're the game. You're being played.
你對我百般討好就是為了獲取我的信任
And your pathetic attempts at fawning to gain my trust.
得了吧
I mean, come on.
被你看穿了
You got me.
如果你真的想知道
If you really want to know
如何在拉斯維加斯的舞臺
how a bank in Paris was robbed
搶劫一家巴黎的銀行
from a stage in Las Vegas,
下個月我會出專題節目
my special comes out next month.
或者我可以指控你妨礙公務
Or I could just bring you in on obstruction charges
把你帶進警局強迫你說出來
and force you to tell me.
當然了  除非你想告訴我
Unless, of course, what you're trying to say to me is that
其實你也不知道他們是怎么做到的
you actually don't know how they did it.
表演技巧和舞臺效果
Showmanship and theatrics.
當一個魔術師揮著手說
When a magician waves his hand and says,
這就是魔術發生的地方
"This is where the magic is happening."
真正的戲法正在別處開始
The real trick is happening somewhere else.
誤導觀眾  最基礎的魔術概念
Misdirection. A basic concept of magic.
對魔術的概念沒興趣
Not interested in the concepts of magic.
我只想知道他們怎么搶銀行的
I wanna know how they robbed a bank.
白癡才會覺得他們真的搶了銀行
You're an idiot if you think they robbed a bank.
不過你未必要信我的話
But don't take my word for it.
去巴黎轉一圈怎么樣
How about a trip to Paris?
赫米雅  請把幻行頭盔給我  親愛的
Hermia, the teleportation helmet, please, darling?
你在開玩笑  是吧
You're joking, right?
你到底想不想知道他們怎么做的
You wanna know how they did it or not?
我會把這個戴到你頭上
I'm just gonna put this on your head.
走上去
Step right up.
就這樣
There you go.
現在我們把這個拉下來  安全又舒適
Now we just pull this down all safe and snug.
放輕松
Make yourself comfortable.
可以了
There we go.
準備好去巴黎的話
And when you're ready to go to Paris,
就說出你的魔法咒語吧
just say the magic word.
見鬼
Blow me?
-這樣就可以了                  -一路順風
- That'll suffice.                                                 - Bon voyage.
你好
Bonjour!
我個人喜歡走樓梯到巴黎
I personally prefer to take the stairs to Paris.
歡迎來到光之城市  羅茲探員
Welcome to the City of Light, Agent Rhodes.
呵呵  那你要我戴頭盔做甚麼
Hardy har har. What was with the helmet?
個人惡趣味
My fun.
怎么
What?
沒甚麼
Nothing.
所以他們造了個金庫
So they got a vault set.
沒錯
Yes.
而且完全復刻了
And it's the exact replica
那個法國佬的銀行金庫
of the little French guy's bank.
所以他是個托
So he's a plant.
他只是個棋子  不是托
He was a dupe, not a plant.
他們選擇了他  知道他坐在哪個位子
They chose him. They knew which seat he was in.
不不不  是觀眾選的位子
No, no, no, the audience picked the seat.
當然了  除非  不是觀眾選的位子
Unless, of course, the audience didn't pick the seat.
他們讓觀眾以為位子是自己選的
They let them think they picked the seat.
我們會隨機抽選一位
We'll choose one at random then.
實際上  他們把事先準備好的球
Actually, they were just palming the ball
藏在掌心用來替換
with the seat number they wanted.
我們在找的是  第5排
We are looking at row number 5.
亨莉  能告訴我座位的號碼嗎
Henley, could I please have a seat number?
幸運數字13
Lucky number 13.
你能確認這個就是你的座位號碼嗎
Could you just confirm that this is, in fact, your seat?
他是早就被選中的
He was selected.
他們給他下了暗示讓他去拉斯維加斯
They programmed his mind to make him go to Las Vegas.
拉斯維加斯萬歲
Viva Las Vegas.
然後不斷強化這個暗示  直到他成行
And then they kept reinforcing it, until he did.
他們跟蹤他
They trailed him.
研究他
They studied him.
這一切都不是靠運氣
Nothing was left to chance.
我量到他的數據了
I got his measurements.
他根本不知道自己已經成了目標
He had no idea he was their target.
他們只要在維加斯把他激活就行了
And they simply activated him in Vegas.
只要我一打響指
When I snap my fingers...
再次介紹  梅利特 McKinney
And once again, Merritt McKinney.
但是他們如何知道他是哪個銀行的
But how did they know what bank was his?
-你開玩笑吧                  -真的嗎
- You're kidding.                                         - Really?
你還能再臭屁點兒嗎
Can you be any more of a condescending ass?
能
Yes.
比如像這樣
Like this.
魔術師用一種非常罕見和神秘的方法
There's a very rare, very mysterious way
來占卜觀眾開戶的銀行
in which a magician divines an audience member's bank.
準備好了嗎
You ready?
是的
Yes.
信用卡
Credit card.
所以他們也是這樣拿到了卡上的簽名
And that's how they got the signature for the card
然後留在了巴黎的金庫裡
they left in the vault in Paris.
非常好
Very good.
你被人領先了  羅茲探員
You're being one-upped, Agent Rhodes.
但是他們還得把簽了名的牌放進金庫啊
Okay, but they had to get the signature card in the vault.
你剛才說他們沒有偷那些錢
You said they didn't steal the money.
不  我沒有這樣說
No, I didn't say they didn't steal the money.
我只說他們沒有搶劫銀行
I said they didn't rob the bank.
我的猜測是他們盯上了
My guess is that they targeted
運鈔車上一批剛印出來
a shipment of freshly minted money
準備送往法國人銀行的鈔票
headed to the Frenchman's bank on-board an armored truck.
當然  要想進去也非常困難
Which, of course, is just as hard to break into.
除非你已經身在其中了
Unless you're already inside.
盡管銀行不會承認
And despite what the banks would have you believe,
這些開車的人精神都不太好
the men who drive these trucks are not exactly mental giants.
對我們的幾位騎士來說
For our Horsemen,
這簡直是小菜一碟
it was almost too easy.
帥哥們
Hey, boys.
那他們是如何讓金庫裡的假鈔消失的呢
So, how did they make the fake money disappear from the vault?
那是甚麼
What is that?
閃光紙
Flash paper.
閃光紙：經過特別加工內含硝酸纖維素的紙張
對熱力極為敏感  點燃後會閃現火焰而不留灰燼
這是魔術師的最愛
Magicians use it all the time.
沒有煙霧  不留痕跡
Creates no smoke, leaves no residue.
該死
Ah merde!
兩天前  他們還默默無聞
Two days ago, no one heard of these guys,
但今晚表演的票35秒內便被搶購一空
but tonight's show sold out in 35 seconds.
我想他們已經向世人解釋了表演的真諦
I think these guys have cracked the secret to show business.
那就是為觀眾送上300萬
Give your audience $3 million.
至少他們會有好心情嘛
Puts 'em in a good mood, doesn't it?
史上最棒結局
Best finale ever.
他們是魔術師中萬裡挑一的理想床伴
They're gonna be the first magicians in history to get laid.
指飛機失事
記住  如果座位上方的氧氣面罩落下
Remember, if the oxygen mask comes down,
-先給律師帶上  別忘了                  -沒錯
- put it on the lawyer first. Remember.                           - Oh, yes.
我就是這么做的  先給律師
I always do. It's lawyer first,
-然後我自己  最後給孩子                  -然後你自己
-then myself and then the children.                                   - Then yourself.
嗯  最後才是孩子
Yes. Then the children.
我來說說咱倆一直共同思考問題吧
Allow me to make plain what we've both been thinking.
甚麼問題
And what's that?
很明顯  你對丹尼爾很有好感
Well, obviously, you have feelings of affection for Daniel.
不求回報還一往情深
Unrequited and misguided,
因為他根本就是情感無能
owing to his lack of emotional availability.
因此  你便十分...
Consequently, you're very tightly...
怎么說呢
How should I put it?
憋著
Corked.
是嗎
Oh, I am?
現在  既然你的生理需求得不到滿足
Now, recognizing that you have physical needs not being met,
本著友愛互助的原則
and strictly in the vein of helping a sister out,
你可以考慮一下讓我做你的  私人鑽洞器
I invite you to think of me as your own personal corkscrew.
我謝謝你
Wow. Thanks.
讓我好好考慮一下你說的廉價且無聊的性愛建議
Let me mull over that offer of cheap and meaningless sex.
廉價且無聊  但也高效省時啊
Cheap and meaningless, maybe, but not time-consuming.
我們可能會提前幾分鐘抵達
We should be getting there a few minutes early.
請坐好  放輕松
So, sit back, relax.
我們即將在新奧爾良著陸
We should be in the Big Easy soon.
Big Easy：新奧爾良別稱
再次感謝您乘坐本次航班
Appreciate you flying with us today.
對特萊斯勒來說這事除了錢還能得到甚麼
So, what's in it for Tressler, besides the money?
還能自我滿足
Ego.
來  選一張牌
Okay, pick your card.
看一下  再放進去  然後告訴我
Look at it, put it in the deck, and tell me.
不對  別告訴我
No, don't tell me.
-好                  -好
-Okay.                                -Okay.
撒迪厄斯那晚就在現場
Thaddeus was there that night.
他完全明白他們是怎么做到的  那他呢
He knows exactly how they pulled it off. What about him?
你說甚麼呢
What are you saying?
你覺得他們是一伙的
You think they could be working together.
我不知道  我只知道他們
I don't know. All I know is that these guys
都是街頭魔術師
were a bunch of street magicians
一年以前還各自單打獨斗
a year ago with no resources.
那如果沒有外界的某種幫助
So, how do they go from doing that to this
他們是如何從街頭魔術師變成了現在的名人呢
without some kind of outside help?
這是你選的那張牌嗎
Is this your card?
不是  它在你旁邊家伙的大腿上待著呢
No, my card is sitting over there in that guy's lap.
牌洗得真不錯
Nice shuffle.
其實  這個很難的
You know, this is hard.
這本書上說
According to this book,
有些人每天花八個小時
some of those guys practice
只練習一個簡單動作  年復一年
one simple move eight hours a day for years.
真的嗎  這幫人真該找點正經事做了
Really? Some of those guys seriously need to get a life.
你是對所有的魔術師都有意見嗎
Is it magicians, in general, you have a problem with?
還是只對這幾個人有看法
Or specifically those guys?
整體來說我對魔術師一點都不感冒
I could care less about magicians in general.
我只是討厭那些利用別人的人
What I hate is people who exploit other people.
怎么利用別人
Exploit them how?
再選一張
Try again.
利用別人的弱點
By taking advantage of their weaknesses.
利用其需求使其相信一些無法解釋的事物
Their need to believe in something that's unexplainable
來忍受生活中的磨難
in order to make their lives more bearable.
在我看來那是一種力量
I see it as a strength.
相信魔術讓我的生活更加開心
My life is happier when I believe that.
這是你選的牌嗎
Is this your card?
是
Yeah.
真的
Yeah?
-對啊                  -太帥了
- Yeah.                                              - Cool.
你臉上掛著的笑容是真的嗎
That smile on your face. Is it real?
也許
Maybe.
我來問問你  探長大人
So let me ask you, Mr. Detective Man.
你覺得你被利用了
Do you feel exploited?
還是其實你也得到了一點點樂趣
Or did you have maybe a tiny, tiny bit of fun?
有個人去看醫生
Guy goes to the doctor.
醫生說  先生 你不能再手淫了
Doctor says, "Sir, you're gonna have to stop masturbating."
那人問  為甚麼
He Says, "Why?"
因為我沒法在你打飛機的時候給你看病啊
He says, "So I can finish the examination."
丹尼  咱們能不能話幾秒鐘談談
Oh, Danny, can I talk to you about
-表演中我的角色問題                  -當然  沒問題
-my role in the show real quick?                             - Yeah, yeah, yeah. Sure.
各位
Hey, guys.
我們還要準備演出呢
We got a show to prepare for.
現在就開始嗎
Do we now?
別別別  別跟我來這個
No, no, no, don't do that.
別想對我用你那套  不行
You're not doing that thing to me. No.
我哪一套  我只是看看你而已
What thing? I'm just looking at you.
真的才怪  我已經觀察你一年了
No, you're not. I've been watching you for a year.
我了解你的那些小把戲
I know all of your little tricks.
你就是這么想的  小把戲
That what they are to you? Tricks?
沒錯  都是小花招  這是巴納姆說的
Yes, it's gimmicks. It's Barnum statements.
全名費尼爾司·泰勒·巴納姆：美國馬戲團經紀人兼演出者
就是看看眼神  讀讀肢體語言啊  我懂的
It's reading the eyes. Body language. I get it.
如果真有你說的那么容易  你來試試亨莉如何
If it's such an easy thing, why don't you do Henley?
對啊  丹尼  來讀讀我的過去吧
Yeah, Danny. Why don't you do me?
不  讀你太簡單  我要嘗試一下解讀賈斯敏
No, you're too easy. I'll do Jasmine.
不
No.
來看看我吧
Do me.
對  沒錯  解讀一下亞瑟
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Do Art.
好吧
Okay.
更簡單了
Even better.
-亞瑟                  -沒錯
- Art.                                         - Yeah.
但我可警告你  只要我愿意
But I warn you, I can be difficult to read,
你想讀懂我很難
when I want to be.
您就跟著我的節奏來吧
Just stay with me, okay?
亞瑟  你小時候很壞
So, Art, you were a tough kid.
是個不折不扣的小流氓
You know, kind of a real rapscallion.
你養了一條狗  也是條惡狗
You had a dog. A real tough dog.
十分兇惡  比如一條真正的...
A brutish breed. Like a real...
我猜測  叫本的斗牛犬
I want to say, Ben the bulldog.
其實  我小時候很瘦弱
Actually, I was a prissy little tot.
我養了一條毛茸茸的白貓叫斯納芙
I had a fluffy white cat called Snuffles.
抱歉
Sorry.
等一下  我再試一次
Wait, let me try one.
-我會做的更好的                  -讓他試
- I can do way better than that.                      - Let him do it.
來吧 讓我再試試  再試一次
Come on, give me one more time. One more time.
他會做得更好的
He can do way better than that.
我們說說你的家人吧
Let's do family.
你有個舅舅
You had an uncle on your mother's side.
他的名字  極具男性魅力
He had a real, kind of... A real masculine name.
一個聽起來很像社會精英的名字
A real, kind of, salt-of-the-earth...
一個  十分親近的
You know, a real stick-it-to-you...
比如保羅  或者湯普森  是保羅嗎
Like it was some kind of Paul. Thompson? Was it a Paul...
算了吧  我放棄  我甚麼都沒看出來
Okay. You know what? I got nothin'.
-差一點                  -真的嗎
- Nearly though.                                 - Was I?
沒錯  我舅舅叫庫什曼·阿米蒂奇
Yeah. My uncle's name was Cushman Armitage.
真的假的
Really?
叫斯納芙的貓和叫庫什曼·阿米蒂奇的舅舅
Snuffles and Cushman Armitage?
那就是你的童年
That was your childhood?
希望今晚的演出比剛才的表現好
I certainly hope tonight's show is gonna be better than this.
別擔心  等著瞧吧
Don't worry. Just you wait.
拜托  告訴我你已經訂到房間了
Hey. Come on, give me some good news on a hotel room, please.
甚麼  開玩笑吧
What, are you kidding me?
不  現在可是狂歡節  迪倫
No, it's Mardi Gras, Dylan.
根本找不到能看到劇場的房子
There's nothing within sight of the theater.
稍等一下  等下  那個女人去哪兒了
Hold on a second. Hold on. Where is this woman?
終于找到你了
Hey, hey! There you are.
你一個法國妞兒剛到
What, the French girl doing a little sightseeing
新奧爾良觀光去了嗎
while she's in New Orleans?
不  其實在這裡  會說法語是一種財富
No. In fact, here, speaking French is actually an asset.
你看到那兒那個女人了嗎
Do you see that woman up there?
那是瑪麗·克萊爾
That's Marie Claire.
她可以為我們提供一間舒適的公寓
And she has a lovely apartment for us.
不用謝
You're welcome.
好吧
Yeah.
我們找到住的地方了
We got a place.
這裡一邊兩個  剩下的30個守在周圍
I want two each inside of here. The other 30 around here.
屋頂  巷道  陽臺等
Roofs, alleys, balconies.
-要時刻盯緊那些魔術師                  -是  長官
- Eyes on The Horsemen at all times.                                       - Yes, sir.
100年前  威廉·羅賓森改名程連蘇
Wow, 100 years ago, William Robinson took the name Chung Ling Soo
威廉·羅賓森：1861-1918，美國魔術師，後用藝名程連蘇
且余生再未公開講過英語
and spent his entire life never speaking English in public.
還有一個人叫馬克西米利安
This other guy, Maximillian...
我現在對魔術的歷史不感興趣
I am not interested in a history lesson on magic at this moment.
如果你還想被他們掌控在手心裡  你繼續
If you want to keep playing into their hands, go for it.
我只是想試著理解他們的思維
I'm just trying to understand how they think.
你認為我被他們玩弄在鼓掌之間是嗎
You think I'm playing in their hands, do you?
我只是不明白那個和這個有甚麼沖突
I don't know how any of that is gonna go against this.
這個甚麼  魔術嗎
This what? This magic?
萊昂納爾·施萊克
Lionel Shrike.
在中央公園  讓一個人選張牌並簽名
In Central Park, he has a guy pick a card and sign it.
然後他走向一棵已經在那兒長了20年的樹
Then he goes to a tree that has been there 20 years.
他們把樹鋸成兩半
They saw the tree in half.
樹中心裹著一個玻璃罐
Inside the tree, encased in glass,
其中就鑲嵌著那張簽過名的紙牌
is the card with the signature.
他是怎么做到的
How did he do that?
我不知道  但肯定有一個合理的解釋
I have no idea. But I'm sure there's a logical explanation.
請讓一下
Excusez-moi
你有派人在大廳盯著嗎
You guys got a guy in that lobby yet?
沒有  但是我有個好消息告訴你
No, but I do have some good news.
還記得阿特拉斯有控制癖吧
Remember how Atlas is such a control freak,
他讓整個團隊都帶了追蹤手鐲
he's got his whole crew on those tracking bracelets?
甚麼追蹤手鐲
What tracking bracelets?
他讓每個團隊成員
He has every member of his crew
都戴上了一副追蹤手鐲
wearing a tracking bracelet.
這些手鐲都以副八平帶半導體制成
Those bracelets are on a sub-8 flat-band.
只要阿特拉斯在追蹤他們
So as long as Atlas is tracking them,
下一個
Next.
我們的人在這個遠程指揮中心內
our boys can track Atlas from right here
就能追蹤阿特拉斯
in the mobile command unit.
好  有消息就通知我
Okay, call me if you get any movement.
收到
Copy that.
你沒有看到全局  迪倫
You are missing the big picture here, Dylan.
巴黎有個地方  叫藝術之橋
There is a place in Paris, Pont des Arts.
清晨時我偶爾會去橋上的長凳上坐會兒
Sometimes in the mornings I sit on a bench there.
看人們許愿
And I watch the people make a wish
在橋上掛鎖
and lock it in a lock on the bridge.
然後把鑰匙扔進塞納河
Then throw the key into the Seine.
整天都是這樣
All day they do this.
有母親  有戀人  也有老人
Mothers, lovers, old men.
看著鑰匙沉入河底
Watching the key sink into the water
秘密也就隨之永遠緊鎖
and their secret is locked away forever.
很真實  也很神奇
Real and, at the same time, magical.
那么
So,
你真覺得還有第五個騎士嗎
do you really think it's possible there's a fifth Horseman?
沒錯
Yeah.
和撒迪厄斯·布雷德利一起  揭開魔術的神秘面紗
傳說中古埃及曾有一個神秘的團體
There is a legend of a secret order born in ancient Egypt called
名為"魔眼"
"The Eye."
據稱  其成員會苦練手上功夫
It is said they perfected sleight of hand
從法老那裡偷取食物
to steal food from the Pharaohs
接濟奴隸
and give it to the slaves.
他們的目的是甚麼呢
Their purpose?
用魔法和幻覺來平衡正義的天平
Using magic and illusion to even the scales of justice.
這幾位天啟騎士們
Are The Horsemen next in
是否和一眾蠢人一樣相信這個神話呢
a long line of fools to believe this myth?
他們是會像在拉斯維加斯時一樣
Will they evade the rules of law and logic
再次從法律和邏輯的約束下成功脫身
like they did in Las Vegas?
還是這片南部沼澤地中的暗黑秘術
Or will the dark mysticism of this Southern swampland
更勝一籌
get the better of them?
說的好  布雷德利先生
Bravo, Mr. Bradley.
除非你有禁止令
Either you have a cease-and-desist,
我猜你沒有  否則請你離開
which you don't, or you should leave.
只要我想停止某件事情
If I want something to cease or desist,
沒有禁令也得停止
it does.
休息一下
Take five.
據你的潛在贊助商說
According to your potential backers,
從這部最出色的的片子中
you stand to make 2.5 million tops
你最多可以掙250萬
from your best special.
我這裡有張支票
I have here a check
上面是350萬
for 3.5 million.
讓我走開
To walk away?
是飛走  我的私人飛機隨時可供調遣
To fly away. My jet is at your disposal.
別開玩笑了  特萊斯勒先生
Let's not kid ourselves, Mr. Tressler.
你想把他們捧出名
You're in this to ride them up.
而我就是要讓他們名聲掃地
I'm in it to ride them down.
看來我們是談崩了
I take it that we do not have a deal.
這也是我們之間的矛盾
And therein lies our conflict.
我就不繞彎子了
Let me be blunt.
我比你有錢的多
My bank account is much, much bigger than yours.
我的律師團隊也更強大
And my lawyers are much stronger.
他們會用各種各樣的禁令
And they will manacle you
讓你寸步難行
with so many injunctions.
直到你站在一旁
Until you stand by,
無助地看著你所擁有的一切
hopelessly watching everything that you own
在你貪婪的眼前漸漸失去
drain away in front of your greedy little eyes.
這也不是我第一次受到威脅了
This isn't the first time I've been threatened.
可我還是好好地站在這
And I'm still here.
不過  你可是第一次被我威脅
It is, however, the first time you've been threatened by me.
如果你做任何不利于我投資的事情
And if you do anything to sully my investment,
像你說的  讓他們聲名掃地的話
the ride down, which you mentioned,
會立刻  馬上惹出一場嚴重的禍事
will be sudden, precipitous, and measurable on the Richter scale.
你可不該那么做
You shouldn't have done that.
據迷信說法
According to superstition,
如果有人用人偶表達自己的憤怒
one who uses a doll to enact one's own wrath,
就會把此憤怒帶給自己
is likely to bring that very wrath unto himself.
很好笑嗎
Isn't that funny?
我還以為你不信魔法
And I thought you didn't believe in magic.
幫我個忙
Do me a favor.
現在想象一下你最刺激的性愛體驗
Visualize your most adventurous sexual experience.
別試著鉆進我腦子裡來  你個變態
Stay out of my head, you perv.
不  如果我不讀你的思想
Well, no, if I stay out of your head,
就沒法變成你的床伴
I'm never gonna get into your pants.
-好吧                  -那咱們還是繼續這個實驗吧
- Right.                                                - So let's stick with this exercise.
-這有助于...                  -恕我冒昧
- And it helps...                          - Pardon the intrusion.
我祝各位今晚一切順利
I just wanted to wish you good luck tonight.
你就可以試著在你那個小網站上拆我們的臺了
What, so you can try to expose us later on your little website?
那是應觀眾要求
And on demand.
-那不可能發生的                  -是嗎
- That's not gonna happen.                            - Oh, no?
因為魔眼而用一架特別的飛機變魔術嗎
Operating on a special plane because of The Eye?
聽說那地方很不錯  皓月千裡  星光燦爛
I heard it's a lovely place. Lots of starshine and moonbeams.
讓所有魔術師夢想成真
Make any magician's wish come true.
你已走了很長的路
You've come a long way,
比任何無名小卒和過氣明星都要長
much further than anyone would have expected of a bunch of wanna-bes and has-beens.
過氣明星如果指的是我的話
If by "Has-been" You're referring to me,
我只想說  受寵若驚
I just wanna say I'm flattered,
因為我總覺得自己從未出名
because I always considered myself a never-was.
介意我在你身上用一下讀心術嗎
Do you mind if I do a quick read on you?
當然可以
By all means.
好的  我看到一個小男孩
Okay, I'm picturing a little boy.
他希望有一天能成為一名偉大的魔術師
He wants to be a great magician someday.
但盡管他還不賴  可還是不夠出色
And though he's good, he's not quite good enough.
最後在娛樂圈的底層結束夢想
So he ends up at the bottom of the entertainment food chain,
吃著那些他永遠無法企及的天才們的殘羹剩飯
feeding off of those who have the talent that he never did.
告訴我  我說得對嗎
Tell me. Am I getting close?
等等  你走之前  我正在研究一個新東西
Wait. Before you go. I'm working on something new.
你有時間嗎
Do you have a second?
好的  選張牌
Okay. Name a card.
-紅心K                  -猜到了
- King of hearts.                              - Knew it.
好的
Okay.
-在你左袖管裡                  -是嗎
- It's up your left sleeve.                                    - Is it?
沒有沒有  我沒看到
No. No, I don't see it up there.
為甚麼不在你那用不到的平絨口袋裡找一下
You know, why don't you check your unnecessary velveteen pocket there?
就是它
Yeah.
滾你的
無論如何  十分感謝你的到來
Anyway, thank you so much for coming by,
但這個休息室是天才專用的  所以
but this is kind of a talent only area, so...
祝你們演出成功
Break a leg.
祝你出門遇鬼
Hey, you break something, too.
女士們先生們
Ladies and gentlemen,
歡迎光臨薩沃伊酒店
the Savoy management welcomes you
來欣賞今晚這場特別的表演
to tonight's special performance,
天啟四騎士  第二幕
The Four Horsemen, Act Two.
不同于以往的表演
Unlike traditional performances,
天啟四騎士支持您進行錄影
The Four Horsemen encourage you to film,
及打電話給親友
call your friends,
可以任意把演出視頻上傳到服務器、發推特
upload, stream, and tweet the show freely.
謝謝  表演即將開始
Thank you. The show will begin in a few minutes.
手錶不錯
Nice watch.
這是我的傳家寶
It's a family heirloom.
對了  我知道他怎么做的
By the way, I know how he did that trick.
-誰                  -施萊克
- Who?                                        - Shrike.
他14歲的時候
So, when he was 14,
看見中心公園大樹上有個洞
he saw a hole in a tree in Central Park.
他讓一名旋轉木馬的工作人員
He had a guy who worked at the carousel
在牌上簽名  就像尋常的戲法那樣
sign a card for what looked like a routine little trick.
然後呢
And?
18年後的  這個工人要退休了
At the guy's retirement, 18 years later,
施萊克開始了他的魔術  他讓同一個人再簽了一次名
Shrike performs, has the guy sign a card,
然後音樂加速  渲染氣氛
and presto!
大家發現  牌到了樹裡面
The card is in the tree.
它在樹裡面18年
It was in the tree for 18 years.
一直都在樹裡面
The card was in the tree.
樹包裹著牌長了18年
The tree grew around the card in 18 years.
我的意思是那不是魔術  一點也沒魔法
I mean, that isn't magic. It's not magic.
其實關鍵在於  魔術不能靠近看
The point is, the trick was not to look closely.
這裡語帶雙關，還有一層意思是：要把眼光放長遠
看上去似乎很久遠
It was to look so far
我們回過頭看看20年前
that you see 20 years into the past.
施萊克溺水後  尸體一直沒被找到
After Shrike drowned, they never found the body.
你想表達甚麼
What are you suggesting?
由亞瑟·特萊斯勒帶來
Arthur Tressler presents
杰克·瓦爾德
Jack Wilder,
亨莉·裡維斯
Henley Reeves,
梅利特·麥金尼
Merritt McKinney,
以及丹尼爾·阿特拉斯
and Daniel Atlas.
天啟四騎士
The Four Horsemen.
謝謝  開始之前
Thank you. Before we begin,
我們要特別介紹兩個人
we'd like to single out two people in particular.
我們想把今晚的表演
A man and a woman to whom
送給這位男子和這位女士
we'd like to dedicate tonight's performance.
聯邦調查局特工迪倫·羅茲
FBI Agent Dylan Rhodes
和經驗稍顯不足的可愛的
and the lovely, if somewhat inexperienced,
國際刑警艾爾瑪·德雷  各位
Interpol Agent Alma Dray, everyone.
對  羅茲特工發誓要抓住我們
Yeah, Agent Rhodes has personally vowed to "Nail us."
如果他足夠機智勇敢的話  我們也支持他
And we encourage him to do so if he has the brains and the fur.
魔術是甚麼
What is magic?
要我們說的話  只不過是有針對性的欺騙
Our argument, nothing but targeted deception.
所以我想讓你們看
So I want you to look.
盡可能近的觀看
Look as closely as possible.
因為你即將觀看的把戲
Because the tricks you are about to see
也許看起來毫無聯系
may not seem connected.
但我們向您保證  它們是聯系在一起的
But we assure you, they are.
接下來進行的到底是100個不同的把戲
Is what follows 100 different tricks?
還是一個巨大的幻覺呢
Or is it one giant illusion?
現在表演的是書本上最古老的把戲之一
And now for one of the oldest tricks in the book.
丹尼  麻煩開一下箱子
Danny, if you wouldn't mind opening up the box,
給大家看看  這裡面空空如也
and showing everybody that it's completely empty.
我們需要12名勇敢的志愿者
Now, we're gonna need 12 courageous volunteers.
我要把這裡的可愛小絨絨
I'm gonna take sweet little Fluffy here,
放到這個神秘的盒子裡
and put her inside this mystery box.
外面有兩支鉛筆
There are two pencils out there.
高舉起它  讓我看見
Hold 'em up high. Let me see 'em.
-這裡                  -對
- Here!                                    - Yeah!
現在你來說出咒語
And now, you will say the magic word.
急急如律令
Abracadabra.
Abracadabra: 西方魔術表演中常用的咒語，源自希伯來語
對  然後我隨便揮一下
Yes, and I will wave this magic wand
這支魔棒  然後
for no reason. And then...
絨絨就在你們眼前神奇地消失啦
Fluffy has magically vanished before your very eyes.
要是你沒有試過集體催眠的話
If you haven't experienced mass hypnosis,
你即將體驗了
you're about to.
睡著
And sleep.
下去下去  睡覺睡覺  完全睡著
Down, down. Sleep, sleep. Completely sleep.
好的  很好  睡覺睡覺
Good, good. Sleep, sleep.
而今晚我們將要
And now we are gonna debunk
揭開一些魔術的秘密
a few magic myths this evening.
我們都知道其實絨絨活得好好的
We all know that Fluffy is, in fact, alive and well.
而且已經神奇地出現了
And Fluffy has miraculously appeared.
只因為有鏡子
As has the mirror
就把箱子呈現出空無一物的狀態
which makes the box only appear as though it's empty.
當你們聽到"不許動"
When you hear the word "Freeze"
我們都變成橄欖球選手
you are all football players.
而你們的工作就是阻截
And your job is to tackle,
大卸八塊
dismantle,
壓碎
crush,
撕碎
tear limb from limb,
四分衛
the quarterback.
我們都聽說過從帽子裡變出兔子的
Now, we've all heard of pulling the rabbit out of the hat.
但有人聽說過從兔子裡變出帽子的嗎
But has anyone heard of pulling a hat out of a rabbit?
你會知道誰是四分衛
You will know who the quarterback is.
那個人會說出這個詞
He will be the one saying that word.
"不許動"
Freeze.
三  二  一
Three, two, one...
把手放到中間  一  二  三
Put your hands in the middle. One, two, three...
干掉四分衛
Kill the quarterback!
回到你們的座位
Get on back to your seats.
我有預感我們很快會再次相見
I got a feeling I'm gonna be seeing you soon.
你掉秤了吧
I guess you have lost some weight.
中途休息時
At the intermission,
我們讓你們將你們寫下現在的銀行余額
we asked you to write down your current bank balance,
然後封在信封裡
and seal it in an envelope.
現在該拿出那些信封了
Now it's time to take those envelopes out.
各位請把它拿出來
Everyone take 'em out.
現在  各位
Now, everybody,
大喊你們的名字  一起喊  來
shout out your name. All at once. Go.
大喊出來
Shout 'em out.
克萊門特·弗蘭尼克
Clement? Frannick?
-對  在這                  -真夠上面的
- Yeah! Up here!                            - Oh. Way up there.
好  迪娜·羅伯遜
Okay. Dina? Robertson?
是我
That's me!
好  喊名字  喊名字  來
Okay. Names. Names. Let's go.
約瑟法·希基
Josepha Hickey?
是我
That's me!
約瑟法  我想讓你盯好自己的余額
Josepha, I want you to focus on your balance,
然後大聲地從一數到十
and count from one to 10 out loud.
一  二  三  四  五
One, two, three, four, five...
停
Stop.
第一個數字是五嗎
Is the first digit 5?
對
Yes.
再來  這次再快點
Do it again. This time, faster.
一  二  三  四  五  六
One, two, three, four, five, six...
停
Stop.
六  再來
Six. Again.
一  二
One, two...
約瑟法  你今天的余額是562美金嗎
Josepha, is your bank balance $562 as of today?
對  是這么多
Yeah. That's what I got.
不幸的是  你說錯了
Unfortunately, you're wrong.
好的  迪娜
Okay, Dina,
一千
One,
四百
Four.
七十
Seven.
-七塊                  -對
-Seven.                                    - Yeah.
你覺得是  但其實你也錯了
You think it is. But in fact, you, too, are wrong.
克萊門特
Clement.
你賬戶裡的不是六千五美金
You do not have $6,500 in your account.
其實  所有人起立  所有人
In fact, everybody stand up. Everybody.
對  把信封放在前額
Yeah. Put your envelopes to your forehead.
盯緊你的數字
Focus on your number.
這是...天哪  跟我害怕的一樣
This is... Oh, dear. Just as I feared.
真奇怪
Oh, this is strange.
我不想這么說  但是你們都錯了
You know, I hate to say this, but you're all wrong.
你們每個人所以為的賬戶裡的金額
Every last one of you is dead wrong
全部都錯到家了
about what you think is in your account.
好  你們現在可以坐下了
Okay, you can sit down now.
對  我差點忘了
Yeah. I almost forgot.
如果沒有偉大的贊助人亞瑟·特萊斯勒
This evening would not be possible
也就不會有今晚的表演
if it weren't for our great benefactor Arthur Tressler.
掌聲  掌聲
Big applause! Big applause!
亞瑟  到臺上來進行閉幕表演吧
Art, actually, why don't you come up on stage for the finale?
-下來  亞瑟                  -下來  亞瑟
- Come on down, Art!                          - Come on down, Art!
他來了  好  很好
There he goes. Okay, good.
我們準備就緒了嗎
Are we on red?
準備就緒  全員待命
Bright red. We're all standing by.
好的  不許任何人離開劇院  誰也不行
All right, no one leaves the theater. No one.
他來了
There he goes.
亞瑟  你填了信封了嗎
Now, Art, did you fill out your envelope?
不用了  我們幫你填了
Well, no need. We've done it for you.
亞瑟  我猜猜
Now, Art, I took a guess.
140多  對嗎
North of 140. Am I right?
順便說一句  那是一億四千萬
That's 140 million, by the way.
抱歉  梅利特
I'm sorry, Merritt.
別人的都錯了
How can he be right about his balance
他的余額怎么對了呢
and everyone else be wrong?
我覺得可能因為他也錯了
I think possibly because he, too, is wrong.
所有人  拿出你們的紙
Everybody, take out your paper.
用你們座位下面的手電筒
And using the flashlight under your seat,
開始給紙加溫
start to warm up that paper.
你們的正確余額開始顯現了吧
I think your correct balance begins to appear.
亞瑟  別擔心  我們給你準備了一個手電筒
Now, Art, don't worry, we have a flashlight for you.
對
Yes.
瞧
Look.
發生甚麼了  丹尼爾
What's going on there, Daniel?
等等  真奇怪  一秒鐘之前
Wait. This is weird. A second ago, it said
是144579651美金
$144,579,651.
但現在
But now...
少了七萬美金
Now it says $70,000 less.
約瑟法  能起身嗎
Josepha, can you stand up?
好的
Yes.
你的新數字是多少呢
Now, what is your new number?
我的賬戶現在是70562美金
$70,562 now in my account.
會不會是約瑟法的余額增加的
Is it possible that Josepha's balance went up
剛好是亞瑟變少的金額呢
the exact amount that Art's went down?
瞧這個  又來了
Hey. Check it out. It's happening again.
是嗎
IS it?
還真是
Wow. It is.
亞瑟的賬戶余額又少了28萬
Art's balance has gone down another 280K.
迪娜·羅伯遜  你的數字呢
Dina Robertson? What did yours say?
281477美金
$281,477.
我們有件事要坦白
We have a confession to make.
她說的沒錯  我們撒了點謊
She's right. We lied about something.
對  你們都不是被隨機選中的
Yes. None of you were chosen at random.
你們都有一個共同點
All of you have one thing in common.
這間屋子裡的每一個人都曾是
Everyone in this room was a victim
在卡特裡娜超級颶風襲擊的
of the hard times that
那段艱難歲月的受害者
hit one of America's most treasured cities.
你們中的一些人失去了房子  車子
Some of you lost your houses, your cars.
丟了買賣
Your businesses.
失去了心愛的人們
Your loved ones.
但你們所有人都在同一家公司進行了保險
But all of you were insured by the same company.
特萊斯勒保險
Tressler Insurance.
你們被拋棄了
You were abandoned.
你們因為合同上的漏洞
You were loopholed,
無法得到應有的賠償
out of your settlements.
這所有的都是在做秀  對嗎
This is all for show. Correct?
你說的“所有”是指我們
"All" Meaning we're doing
在觀眾面前展示的這些嗎
it onstage in front of a paying audience?
如果是  對的  這就是一場秀
Then, yes, it's for show.
我銀行賬戶多了八萬兩千美金
I've got $82,000 in my bank account!
我手機上這么顯示的
It says it right here on my cell phone!
各位  現在看看你們的手機  各位
Everybody, look at your cell phones right now! Everybody!
這是真的嗎
Is this for real?
我不知道
I don't know.
真的發生了嗎
Is this happening?
我不知道  我也說不上來
I don't know! I can't tell!
是你們干的嗎
Hey! Did you do this?
我們何德何能  亞瑟
How could we, Art?
我們沒有你的密碼
We don't have your password.
我們沒有訪問數據的權限
We'd need access to information
我們沒法動用你的錢
we could never get our hands on.
噢  是安全問題  比如
Yes, security questions, for instance, like,
我不知道你媽媽婚前的姓氏
I don't know, your mother's maiden name
或者你第一只寵物的名字
or the name of your first pet.
我們哪會有這些信息呢  亞瑟
Where would we get that information, Art?
你絕對不可能告訴我們的
You certainly would never tell us.
我們得到確認了  這是真的  他們搶了他
We got confirmation. It's really happening. They robbed him.
別讓他們跑了
Do not let them get away.
放心，我們給你留了飛機和勞斯萊斯
Hey, we left you the jet and the Rolls.
賠死你個王八蛋
You got hell to pay!
站住
Stop!
站住  所有人都站住
Stop! Nobody move!
不許動
Freeze!
他就是四分衛
Quarterback!
我們是天啟四騎士
We are The Four Horsemen.
晚安
Good night.
把他們從我身上移開
Get 'em off me!
走開  放開我
Get off! Get off me!
放開我
Get off me!
好了  所有人都到外面集合  所有人
All right. I want everyone on the street! Everyone!
-四分衛                  -四分衛
- Quarterback!                              - Quarterback!
富勒  戲院門口碰頭
Fuller, meet me in front of the theater
帶好追蹤器
and bring the tracker.
快  快  立刻  快點
Let's go! Let's go! Now! Come on! Let's go!
給我追蹤器
Give me the tracker.
走
Let's go.
聯邦調查局  讓開
FBI! Clear!
-迪倫                  -媽的
- Dylan!                                       - Damn.
發現甚麼了
What have you got?
這是他  跟著紅點
That's him right there. Follow the red dot.
好的  交給我  包抄他們
All right, I'll take this. Go. Box 'em. Cut 'em off that way.
他在勃艮第大街向左轉
He's turning left on Burgundy.
讓開
Hey! Move!
讓開  讓開
Move! Move!
我發現他在波旁向北移動
I got him heading north on Bourbon.
-抱歉  讓開  讓開                  -站住
- Sorry. Move, move!                                            - Hey!
抱歉  讓下  讓下
Hey, excuse me. Move, move! Excuse me.
我在波旁追丟了他
I've lost him at Bourbon.
該死  你在哪
Damn! Where are you?
讓開
Excuse me.
他在匯兌大樓朝南走了
He's heading south on Exchange Place.
站住
Stop!
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
他要進拿破侖餐廳
He's going in Napoleon House.
讓開  讓開
Move! Move!
讓開
Move out of the way!
Hey!
讓開
Move!
他在洗手間  我抓到他了
He's in the bathroom. I have him in the bathroom.
不不不
No! No! No!
別動
Freeze!
放下武器
Lower your weapons!
甚麼
What?
我追蹤的是我自己
I'm tracking myself!
天啟四騎士讓那些以字母命名的機構
The Horsemen left egg on the face of what they call
無地自容
the alphabet agencies,
我們不禁要質疑
calling into question
聯邦調查局特別的專案組的效率
the efficacy of the FBI's task force
以及此次調查負責人
as well as the man in charge of the investigation,
特別探員迪倫·羅茲
Special Agent Dylan Rhodes,
受到了公眾的嘲諷
who was publicly ridiculed,
今晚他被超過十餘名觀眾撲倒
and even tackled at tonight's performance.
失球了
Talk about a fumble.
fumble: 美式足球中的失去球權，在這裡也暗示他被觀眾當作四分衛
這起事件迅速傳遍全國
This is quickly becoming a national story,
這是天啟四騎士在數日之內
as The Horsemen have now seemingly pulled off the impossible
第二次完成了不可能之舉
for the second time in as many days.
兩天前在拉斯維加斯
Two nights ago in Vegas, The Horsemen
天啟四騎士似乎搶了一家巴黎的銀行
seemingly robbed a bank in Paris...
在做甚麼
What are you doing?
買醉
I'm having a drink.
我來接你了
I came to get you.
我很擔心你
I'm worried about you.
你擔心我  好吧  我還擔心你呢
You're worried about me. Well, I'm worried about you.
阿特拉斯  你抓住他了
Atlas. You had him.
他沒有武器
He didn't have a weapon.
我不能對他開槍  你知道的
I couldn't shoot him and you know that.
是啊  但是你放走了他
Yeah, but you... You let him go.
是吧
Didn't you?
一個漂亮的法國妞突然出現
A pretty French girl shows up out of the blue,
說是我的搭檔  然後她放走了壞人
acts like she's my partner and then she lets the bad guy go?
放手
Let go of my arm.
你到底是誰
Who exactly are you anyway?
我記得你說過你是個坐辦公室的
I thought you said you were a desk agent.
身手不錯
Not bad.
這是甚麼
What is this?
荷魯斯之眼是甚麼
What's the Eye of Horus?
我今晚不想卷入任何事
Oh, certainly nothing I want to get into tonight.
你清醒的時候已經夠輕視我了
You're dismissive enough about me when you're sober.
自己找路回去
Find your way back yourself.
布雷德利先生  特萊斯勒先生邀你共飲一杯
Mr. Bradley? Mr. Tressler would like you to join him for a drink.
先生
Sir.
謝謝
Thank you.
你在他們中扮演甚麼角色
What is your role with them?
角色
Role?
是  你看上去知道他們所有的事
Yes. You seem to know everything about them.
他們要做甚麼  他們要去哪
What they're gonna do. Where they're gonna be.
如果能讓你好過點
If it makes you feel any better,
我會說這和你無關
this wasn't about you.
那請告訴我為甚麼和我無關
Please tell me why this was not about me.
這只是魔術  特萊斯勒先生
This is a magic trick, Mr. Tressler.
全球都有
Played out on a global scale.
您只是他們表演時的咒語
You, sir, are the abracadabra.
是他們偷梁換柱時用來分散注意力的
The distraction, while they set up the real trick.
用我的一億四千萬分散注意力
I was a $140-million distraction?
是的
Yes.
那種非常自我使你第一時間
And that very ego that got
融入他們
you involved with them in the first place
這讓你看不到這一切
is what keeps you from seeing that.
-你知道                  -你能毀了我
- You know...                                   - "I can destroy you."
是的  我知道
Yes, I do know.
但是你不會
Well, you won't.
你也不會毀了他們
And you won't destroy them.
無論這大戲法是甚麼
Whatever this grand trick is,
都是很久以前就設計好的
it was designed a long time ago.
我相信接下來要進行的
And I believe that what's
才是真正令人驚嘆的
about to follow is really going to amaze.
我建議你放輕松  好好享受VIP座位
So I suggest you sit back and enjoy your front row seat.
為此你已經花了很大一筆錢
You paid quite a lot of good money for it.
無論你站在哪邊
Whatever you stand to make
如果你現在曝光他們  毀了他們
I'll double it, if you expose them now.
我給你雙倍
And destroy them.
我站在500萬那邊
I stand to make five million.
我要迴避嗎
Am I flinching?
不用
No, you're not.
抱歉傷了你的膀子
I'm sorry for your arm.
不  該道歉的是我
No. I'm sorry.
我是個混蛋  我喝醉了
I was an asshole. I was drunk.
我現在很茫然
I'm at a loss.
梅利特說我幾乎離不開辦公桌
You know, when Merritt said i hardly spent any time away from the desk,
也許他說得沒錯
he was right.
我的本職工作是一名研究員
I'm a researcher. That's what I do best.
那...這是怎麼一回事情呢？
So what's this all about?
如果你相信的話...據說
Supposedly, if you buy into it,
魔眼是魔術的看守者
The Eye are the keepers of real magic
也是所有魔術師的保護神
and the protectors of those who practice it.
魔術師的接班人
"Candidates for initiations
必須謹記並絕對服從以下命令
"Must follow a series of commands with blind obedience."
-這些傳說荒誕不經                  -但還還是有人相信的
- This isn't real.                                            - But there are some who think it is.
讓我來說明下？
May I?
據文中記載  他們每世紀只接納兩次新人
According to this, they only take new people twice a century.
所以  你的意思是  天啟四騎士做這些表演
So what? The Horsemen are doing these shows
是為了加入魔眼嗎
in order to get into this thing?
-真想不到                  -是想不到
- I don't know.                                   - I don't know.
我的意思是  他們可以直接去搶銀行
I mean, I guess these guys could just rob banks to rob banks.
而沒必要把搶銀行做成一場表演
They don't have to put on a show for that.
這些可能只是神話和虛構出來的故事
It's probably just a myth.
我覺得用常理
But it doesn't make any sense,
很難來解釋他們的所作所為
and I don't think logic will solve this for us.
-所以我是這麼認為的                  -沒錯
- You don't say?                                                                    - No.
很多事情，相隔一些距離才可以看清
I believe that some things are only discovered
當局者迷，旁觀者清
if you take certain leaps.
-嗯，我準備要...                  -嗯，好的
- Well, I gotta get to...                                         - Yeah. Yeah.
-謝謝  晚安                  -晚安
- Thanks. Good night.                      - Yeah. Good night.
-抱歉                  -沒事
- Sorry.                                 - It's all right.
如果魔眼存在
If The Eye did exist,
我們得假設他們正看著我們  對嗎
we'd have to assume they were watching us, right?
該死
Shit.
我覺得是有人在監視我們  但不是魔法
I think someone is watching us, but it isn't magic.
你的擔心沒錯
Your fears are correct.
這個不是原來的手機
This is not and has never been your phone.
它完美的複製了你原先的那個手機，除了這個地方...
It's a clone in every way, except for this.
一個竊聽器
A bug.
有人監視了你所有電話和短信
Someone has heard every call, read every text.
所以他們才能走在我們前面
That's how they were able to stay ahead of us.
該死的
God damn it!
給我審訊阿特拉斯的磁帶
Get me Atlas' interrogation tape.
是，長官。已經放入硬盤了
Yes, sir. I have it on the hard drive.
播放錄像
Picture's up.
快進
Okay, fast forward.
快進  快進  停
Go on, go on. Freeze!
一幀一幀放
Okay. Frame by frame. Go on.
正常速度播放
Play it through.
停  放大  放大
Stop. Zoom in tighter. Tighter.
這個時候  他換了我手機
There. That's where he took my phone.
這玩意兒一直在發送信息嗎？
Is that thing transmitting?
只有你打電話發短信時才會
Only when you're making a call or sending a text.
我已經把竊聽器拆了
Plus I removed the bug.
哦  現在把竊聽器放回手機裡面去  然後開機
All right. Put it back in and turn on the phone.
他們不知道我們發現了竊聽器
They don't know that we know about the bug.
從現在起  我們要趕在他們前面
As of this instant, we are ahead of them.
並且牽著他們的鼻子走  明白嗎
We need to keep it that way. Understand?
用它來找到並追蹤我原先的手機
Find my real phone and track it.
搞定  你原先手機20分鐘前在紐約市區
Already did. As of about 20 minutes ago, it's in New York City.
太好了
Good.
我要突襲他們，斷其退路
I wanna cut 'em off at the knees.
魔力？切斷
They got power? Cut it.
電話？電？水？都切斷
They got phones, electricity, water? Cut it.
把他們逼入絕境
Squeeze 'em out.
我要讓他們知道我們的厲害
I want 'em to feel our presence.
我要一架飛機
And get me an airplane!
防火牆失效了  難道他們發覺了？
The firewall's down. Do they know about this?
他們指誰？
They who?
他們，就是指我們所效力的人
"They," "Them," Whoever we're working for.
我們為誰效力
Who are we working for?
難不成要我們為他們的行為坐牢？
And are we prepared to go to jail for them?
別胡思亂想了
Stop being paranoid.
但這真的發生了
It really does happen.
在你身上發生  不代表也會在我們身上發生
It happened to you. Doesn't mean it's gonna happen to us.
兄弟，我只知道我不想發生這些事情
Guys, I don't know if I can do this, all right.
我不想蹲監獄  好嗎
I don't want to go to jail, you know?
那就別添亂  你不是總說
Then don't screw up. You're always talking about
想被當作成年男子漢看待嗎？
wanting to be treated like an adult.
現在是你拿出成年人樣子的時候了
Now might be a good time to start acting like one.
按計劃來  你留在這裡  負責把全部資料燒掉
Stick to the plan. Stay here and burn it all.
我不知道我正在幹甚麼
I don't know what I'm doing here.
我只知道你在其他地方甚麼也做不了
I don't know what you would do anywhere else.
我在這裡只是為了那遙不可及的一桶金
I'm here for the pot of gold at the end of the rainbow.
拿到我就走
That's it. Then I'm gone.
結束以後你想干嘛就干嘛  梅利特
You can do whatever you want when this is over, Merritt.
但那之前  你必須遵守計劃
But until then, you stick to the plan.
伙計  他們來了
Hey, guys. They're here.
-我的人準備好了                  -速戰速決
- My guys are ready to go.                           - Let's do this quickly...
-她不能去                  -甚麼
- No.                                                        - What?
她沒有權限
She doesn't have jurisdiction here.
她是國際刑警  讓她跟著我
She's Interpol. She's with me.
她不能去
She stays.
甚麼  甚麼
What? What?
她留在車裡
Stay in the car.
走了
Let's go.
好了  走了
Okay. Let's do it.
聯邦調查局
FBI!
女士優先
Ladies first.
不許動
Don't move!
能告訴我
Tell me.
我的錢花的值得嗎？
Is my money being well-spent?
超值得
Exceedingly well.
那麼你再告訴我
Now you tell me,
你準備怎麼處理這些騎士
how do you like your Horsemen?
燉還是炸？
Fricasseed or fried?
切碎他們
Shredded.
我會叮囑大廚的
I'll tell the Chef.
站住
Freeze!
迪倫
Dylan!
堅持住
Hold on!
你個小...
You little...
你來呀
Come here!
五樓沒問題  現在上六樓
Five is clear. Standing by for six.
你這個小混蛋
You little Shit!
-你在搞甚麼                      -你在搞甚麼
- What game are you playing?                  - What game are you playing?
六樓安全  上七樓
We're all good at six. Move to seven.
收到  上七樓  上..上...
Copy that. Going to seven. Go, go, go!
不不不... 回來
No, no, no, no, no. Go back!
過來
Come here!
好了  等等  等等
All right, hold on, hold on!
-不是吧                    -就是
- Really?                                              - Yup.
你
You...
你個小...
You little...
該死
Shit!
給我
Give me that!
施萊克（Lionel Shrike的）
所有單位  封鎖北邊出口
All units, cover the north exit now!
埃文收到
Clear on Evan.
封鎖所有出口
Block every possible exit.
回來  該死
Hey! Get back. Shit.
-聯邦調查局  算是吧  征用你的車  謝謝                   -甚麼
- FBI. Sort of. I need your car. Thanks.                                                                         - What?
甚麼
What?
停下  停下
Stop! Stop!
很好  跟上他
Good. Follow him!
以後再也不要把我一個人扔在車裡面  永遠
Don't ever tell me to stay in the car. Ever.
那不是我的命令
I didn't have tactical command.
如果你不相信我  就告訴我
If you don't trust me, just tell me.
而且你發誓  以後要幫我說話
Promise me, next time, you will back me up.
我們能不能待會再談
Could we have this conversation later, please?
不能
No!
好吧  我答應你  現在我們走吧
Okay, fine, I promise. Now, go!
-他們去哪了                  -他們去哪了
- Where'd they go?                                    - Where are they?
我不知道  她開了某人的車走的
I don't know. She just took some guy's car.
-他們去哪了                  -那邊  那邊
- Where are they?                              - That way. That way.
-這是你的車嗎                  -是
- Is that your car?                                       Yeah.
我們走
Let's go.
他在那
There he is!
讓開
Move!
左轉
Left!
我們在弗蘭基羅斯福路向東去
We're heading east on the FDR Drive.
-不是向東                  -是向北  向北
- This is not east.                                      - North! North!
-我們正向北開往羅斯福路                      -在搞甚麼
- We're heading north on the FDR Drive.                                            - What?
我們在羅斯福路上方為您發來現場報道
We're coming to you live above the FDR,
正如您所見  紐約市警察和聯邦探員
where NYPD and federal agents, as you now see,
都參與了這場競速追逐
are engaged in a high-speed pursuit,
他們跟在黑色轎車後面
following a black sedan.
富勒  你在哪兒
Fuller, where are you?
就在你後面不遠
Right here. Trying to catch up to you now.
我們正試圖選個更好的位置取景
We're now trying to get you a better shot.
加把勁
Come on!
抱歉
Sorry.
看來他們正開向
It looks like they're turning
第59街大橋
onto the 59th Street Bridge.
只要他們還在我們的視線中
As soon as we have them within range,
我們就會為你帶來現場直播
we will bring you those pictures live.
好樣的  跟緊點兒
Good. Just stay with him.
快快快
Go, go, go!
後面... 你在巴士後面
Behind... You're behind the bus!
超車
Get over!
他媽的
Oh, shit!
出來
Come here!
後退  後退
Get back! Get back!
迪倫  我們走  伙計
Dylan, let's go, man!
快走  你
Come on, you...
-伙計  快出來                -他會死在這兒的
- Come on, man! Get out!                      - He's gonna die in here.
放棄吧  你無能為力的
Leave him! There's nothing you can do!
快走  算了
Let's go! Leave him!
-文件                  -迪倫
- The Paper!                                - Dylan!
我們走  我們走  快走
Let's go! Let's go! Come on!
今天，一場警方開始於唐人街
Today, the unfolding story of
後在59大橋上高速追擊的緝捕行動
a popular and controversial group of magicians,
演變成一個悲劇性結局的故事
who have been fast capturing the public's imagination,
一個譭譽參半、時刻抓住公眾想像力的
took a dark turn when a police action that began in Chinatown
魔術師團隊中的一員，天啟四騎士之一
developed into a dramatic, high-speed chase across the 59th Street Bridge,
杰克·瓦爾德在汽車爆炸中不幸罹
which caused a fatal collision that took the life of Jack Wilder, one of the so-called Four Horsemen.
到目前為止  其他三名成員仍不知去向
The whereabouts of the other three Horsemen remain unknown at this time.
迪倫  他們剛剛調查了杰克車裡的那份文件
Dylan, they just figured out what the paper was in Jack's car.
那他們有甚麼發現嗎  那他們有甚麼發現嗎
So they know what it is? And why the kid died trying to protect it.
-埃文斯會盡快讓我們知道的                     -我們走
-Evans is on his way to brief us right now.                                        - Let's go.
-但你還是先聽下電話                          -誰打來的
-You're gonna wanna take this first, though.                           - What's that?
你的朋友撒迪厄斯·布雷德利
Your friend Thaddeus Bradley.
羅茲
Rhodes.
你應該知道魔術師助手的作用吧  對吧  羅茲探員
You do understand the function of the magician's assistant, don't you, Agent Rhodes?
當魔術師在表演魔術的時候  助手則負責來分散觀眾們的注意力
Yeah, she's there to distract them while he sets up the trick.
看來你還沒有錯的很離譜
You'd be right if you weren't so wrong.
當你在觀看魔術的時候
While you're watching the magician,
卻被那一臉無辜可愛的小美女在操控一切
that lovely innocent is actually pulling the strings.
難道你不覺得奇怪嗎？
Don't you find it peculiar that Interpol would send you
派一個做文員的國際刑警來當你的助手
a first timer off the desk to be your assistant?
為甚麼他會加入這個案子？
Why did she request to be put on the case?
她是被委派來的
She was assigned to the case.
就像在牌堆裡面隨便選張牌，但你抽到了「好牌」
Luck of the draw. Like choosing a random card in the deck.
我很奇怪  你怎麼突然間變得好心起來了  你在打甚麼算盤
I find it odd, your sudden act of generosity. What's in it for you?
我只是想讓游戲更加公平
Just trying to even the game.
否則讓我覺得我是在和一個綁沙袋、帶腳蹼的人在比賽
I feel like I'm playing with somebody wearing ankle weights and flippers.
你要加把勁  羅茲探員... 加把勁
Keep up, Agent Rhodes. Keep up.
我們有麻煩了
We got a problem.
這裡有一個保險箱
Here's the safe.
哦，不..不..不...
No, no, no. Hey.
他來這兒干嘛
What's he doing here?
更準確、更可靠的領導我們破案
Giving us our first solid lead.
我們在調查一個私人保安公司
We've been investigating a private security contractor
他名叫埃爾克霍恩
called Elkhorn
-在過去的5年裡...              -怎么樣
- For the last five years...                                     - And?
他們藏了差不多5億美元在...
They've been hiding close to a half billion dollars...
我沒問你  我在問他
I didn't ask you. I asked him.
那些錢被藏在皇后區的一個倉庫的保險箱裡
The money's in a vault inside a warehouse in Queens.
我們認為保險箱是那些魔術師的最終目標
We think this vault is your magicians' final target.
你從在橋上死掉的那個魔術師那兒拿到的
The magician who died on the bridge you pulled our classified
正是關於埃爾克霍恩的機密文件
Elkhorn file right from his crispy little hand.
除了用一些類似羅賓漢式的花招
And despite their bullshit Robin Hood razzle-dazzle,
羅賓漢 Robin hood：英國民間傳說中劫富濟貧的俠盜式英雄人物
那幫魔術師跟普通盜賊沒甚麼兩樣
your magicians are nothing more than common thieves.
他們怎么拿到那份文件的
How did they get the file?
我想這部分會是你最感興趣的  羅茲探員
This is the part you're gonna find particularly interesting, Agent Rhodes.
當他們在新奧爾良的時候  利用你的手機訪問了移動控制中心
They patched to my server after they accessed your mobile command center in New Orleans
盜取了我們服務器密碼
with codes they got from your phone.
這是由於你當時命令我們全部去追捕所導致的
You ordered us all out to chase after them.
你們在這個案子上所展現的無能程度
The level of incompetence displayed on this case,
其本身就如同一個魔術了
that's a magic trick in and of itself.
所以現在由我來接管這個案子
Abracadabra. I'm taking over.
老大  由他來接手？
Boss, he's taking over?
我們走吧  先生們
Let's go, gentlemen.
我想和你談一下
Hey. I want to have a word with you.
以後別用前面那種口氣和我說話
Don't ever talk to me like that again.
-你究竟為了甚麼而加入這個案件         -甚麼
- Why the hell did you take this case?                                   - What?
美國人有句話：叫知人知面不知心
People say I'm "Hard to read." That's an American expression.
-你明白嗎                    -我明白
-Do you understand it?                                -Yes.
那好  現在我就跟你說清楚
Good, then let me make myself perfectly clear to you.
如果你還在其他地方搞一些小動作的話  我發誓一定會...
If I find out that you are anything other than who you say you are, I swear...
我們法語中也有句話：彼此信任，愚公亦可移山
And we French also have an expression, La foi souleve la montagne.
即信任能戰勝一切
"Faith can move mountains."
如果我們想戰勝天啟四騎士  那你就該對我多那么一點點信任
If we hope to capture The Horsemen, then you need to have a little faith in me.
因為我沒做過甚麼見不得人的事
Because I've done nothing to deserve otherwise.
我剛剛就被人出賣了  這個案子就快不歸我管了
I just got my ass headed to me. I am losing this case.
現在對我來說  信任過於奢侈  我無福消受
So faith is a luxury I don't have any time for right now.
杰克這一生最大的夢想  就是成為最有名的魔術師
More than anything in his life, Jack wanted to be the most famous magician who ever lived.
我不敢說他已實現了夢想  但希望無論他在何處  都可以徜徉在魔術海洋中
And I can't say he achieved it, but I do hope wherever he is, it is full of magic.
-但關鍵是...對不起          -關鍵是...
-But the point is... Sorry.                     -The point is...
我們之所以現在還在這裡...  表示我們絕不放棄
The point of why we are here is to say that we are not... We cannot quit now.
我們已開始實施更宏大的計劃  而且必須成功
We've started something bigger than all of us. We have to finish it.
已逼近倉庫  5隊和6隊分別負責北邊和南邊的入口
Approaching the warehouse. Units 5 and 6 cover the north and south entrances.
我們去保險箱那兒
We are going for the vault.
保險箱在哪裡？保險箱在哪裡？
Hey. Where's the safe? Where's the safe?
-怎么回事             -那該死的保險箱在哪兒
-What is this?                 -Where the hell is the goddamn safe?
你們剛在外面的時候  我們接到埃文斯的命令把它搬出去了
We just moved it while you were outside. Evans' orders.
-甚麼        -我可沒說過
-What?                -I never said that.
長官  你之前打過電話說政府要轉移保險箱
Sir, you got a phone call and said Washington wants the safe moved.
我不可能親口說這些話的  探員
You never heard that come out of my mouth, Agent.
甚麼情況？你告訴我這到底是怎么回事？他媽的太扯淡了
What happened? You tell me what's going on, because this is bullshit!
不
No!
我的上帝...
Jesus Christ.
長官  長官  你在干嘛
Sir? Sir? What are you doing?
這是貝多芬的D大調協奏曲  保險箱在哪
I think it's Beethoven's Concerto in D-Major. Where's the safe?
他的手下正把它搬上貨車
His team is loading the truck.
-攔下那輛貨車          -停下
- Stop the truck!                               - Stop!
-停下             -攔下那輛貨車
- Stop!                        - Hey! Stop that truck!
到底怎么回事  我們是奉命行事
What the hell's going on? We got our orders.
命令改了   現在打開貨車
Now you've got new orders. Open it up.
現在開始全聽我的
Okay. Here's what I want.
他們以為保險箱已經離開這兒了
At this moment, they think that safe's leaving this site.
我們將計就計  跟著它一直到...
So we stay with it. We follow it all the way to...
-這是要送去哪裡？         -博恩茨街5號
-Where's it going?                         -5 Pointz. Up the street.
那我們就去博恩茨街5號
So we go to 5 Pointz.
保險箱到哪兒我們就到哪兒  這玩意會帶我們找到他們
Wherever the safe goes, we go. It'll lead us right to 'em.
你們兩個跟我來
You two are with me.
伙計們
Guys.
上頭打電話讓我們看看這個  20分鐘前騎士們把它上傳到了Youtube
Look. Office just called with this. Horsemen posted it to YouTube 20 minutes ago.
Youtube: 全球最大的視頻分享网站，用戶可上傳、觀看及分享視頻短片
自2009年8月6日，中国大陸一直封鎖Youtube (及Facebook、Twitter)
原因是《中國國防報》指責這三者是西方敵對勢力的宣傳與顛覆工具
我們之所以現在還在這裡...  表示我們絕不放棄
The point of why we're here is to say that we are not... We cannot quit now.
我們已開始實施更宏大的計劃  而且必須成功
We've started something bigger than all of us. We have to finish it.
當你們在現場看我們表演的時候，請同時牢記杰克·瓦爾德這個名字
Remember the name Jack Wilder when you see us live,
我們相約今晚7點  在皇后區博恩茨街5號
5 Pointz, Queens, 7:00.
表演還有半個小時開始  那正是我們現在去的地方
Their show is in a half an hour. It's exactly where we're headed.
說實話，老大，我不想和你唱反調，但那幫家伙真的很狡猾
I don't know, boss. I don't wanna be the naysayer, but these guys are kinda tricky.
羅茲  他們只不過是幾個賣藝人而已
Rhodes, they're entertainers.
之前逃脫的騎士們  將在博恩茨街5號上演絕妙收官演出
A stunning turnout here in 5 Pointz as the renegade Horsemen
這也是給聯邦調查局一記響亮的耳光作為收尾
taunt the FBI into a final showdown.
天啟四騎士邀請我們參與他們與聯邦調查局三輪較量中的最後一戰
The Horsemen have invited us to their final round of their three-act face-off with the FBI.
他們到底留了一手甚麼殺手鐧  我們拭目以待
What do they have in store? We're about to find out.
-所有人盯緊貨車  注意看看誰來接近貨車        -收到
-All eyes on the truck. Let's see who approaches.                        -Copy that.
羅茲探員、富勒
Agents Rhodes, Fuller?
-有甚麼新情況                  -這邊有情況  有人走向卡車
-Go, for us.        -We've got movement. Someone's walking toward the truck.
是個女人
It's a woman.
-不許動             -見鬼
- Freeze!                            - Oh, shit!
發生甚麼事了
What the hell's going on?
這不是那個製作揭穿魔術把戲電視節目的傢伙麼？
Hey! It's the guy from the TV.
-把槍放下        -看呀，原來這是第五名騎士
Put your guns down.
你在開甚麼玩笑？我和你們一樣，也在追蹤他們
Are you kidding? I'm following them, just like you are.
你一直以來都趕在我們前面
I'm not following anybody anymore.
但是這次  我領先你一步  我再也不會跟在別人後面了
You've been ahead of us this whole time. But guess what? I'm ahead of you now.
你束手就擒吧
Your ass is mine.
腦殘  為甚麼放棄治療？
You guys are still idiots.
這兒碰巧是萊昂納爾·施萊克生前排練的場地
This happens to be the former rehearsal space for Lionel Shrike.
也是我第一場表演的地方
It's where I did my first show.
如果你還想繼續出糗的話  就打開保險箱瞧瞧吧
Now, if you wanna look like even bigger idiots, why not open it?
羅茲探員  當你打開時  你能再做一下那個無比困惑的表情嗎
And while you're doing it, Agent Rhodes, would you mind reenacting your look of absolute befuddlement for me?
我很高興用它來作我新DVD的封面
It will make a wonderful cover for my DVD.
-打開保險箱       -去吧      -打開它
-Open the safe.            - Go ahead.              - Open it.
這是甚麼鬼東西
What the hell?
這是甚麼  讓我來
What? Give me that.
不... 不！
No... No!
這是甚麼東西
What is this?
大家退後
Get back!
誰不喜歡精彩的魔術呢
Who doesn't love a good magic trick?
他們又讓你們追著空保險箱疲於奔命
They have you chasing empty safes again.
再一次的   把你們領向了錯誤的方向
Once again, misdirection.
他們馬上就開始了  快行動起來
The show is starting. Move out!
羅茲探員  我現在要問的問題是
The question I'd be asking now, Agent Rhodes is,
真的保險箱去哪兒了
"What happened to the real one?"
清場  快點清場  叫他們讓開  別擋路
Clear! Clear 'em out! Come on. Move 'em out. Move 'em out of the way.
聯邦調查局  給我讓路
FBI! Give me a path!
讓開  讓開
Clear out! Clear out!
甚麼是魔術
What is magic?
魔術是一種騙局
Magic is deception.
但是這騙局給人帶來趣味、娛樂和靈感
But deception designed to delight, to entertain, to inspire.
留神...讓開...注意讓開下
Look out! Clear! Clear! Look out!
-魔術是一種信念、信仰       -以及信任
-It is about belief, faith...                                 -trust.
如果沒有那些特質，作為一種藝術，魔術將名存實亡
Without those qualities, magic, as an art form, would no longer exist.
但是如果這些特質  不是用于崇高的理想
But what happens if these qualities are not used for their higher purpose?
而是用于欺騙  撒謊
And instead they're used to cheat, lie.
或因為一己私欲  或因為欲壑難填
For personal gain or for greed.
那么它就不再是魔術
Then it's no longer magic.
而是一種犯罪
It's crime.
所以今晚  為了我們的終極演出
So tonight, for our final act,
你們將幫助我們一起撥亂反正
you're gonna help us set a few things right.
-到底發生了甚麼  羅茲         我不知道
-What's going on here, Rhodes?                 -I don't know.
好戲開場了
Showtime.
快看
Look!
他們在房頂上  行動  快快快...
There they are on the roof. Let's move! Go, go, go!
-迪倫        -聯邦調查局執行公務
- Dylan!                          - FBI, coming through!
你在這裡做甚麼
What are you doing here?
你心裡清楚  他們的方向錯了
They're going in the wrong direction and you know it.
羅茲  所有人都來  快跟上
Rhodes! I need all personnel now!
你要相信我  堅定你的信念
You need to trust me. Take your leap of faith.
等等
Wait.
-我跟她一起去          -去吧  我支持你  我在這兒等你
- I'm going to go with her.                  - Go. I got your back. I'll be right here.
你們去吧
Go ahead!
出事你負責  富勒
That's on you, Fuller.
快上快上... 快快... 速度...
Let's go, let's go! Now, now, now!
-丹尼爾        -我在
-Daniel?                       -Yeah.
呃... 這么說吧...
As our, let's call it,
我們這一年的冒險生活馬上就要結束了
year of living dangerously comes to a close, in a rare moment of vulnerability,
我想就我們之間友誼說幾句真心話
I'd like to express a sentiment to you about our relationship.
說吧
Okay.
初次見面時  我覺得你是個...
Well, when I first met you, I thought you were kind of a...
-混蛋           -呵呵
- dick.                           - hehe
然後呢
And?
沒有然後  這就是全部
No, that's it.
-你真貼心         -是啊
- That's very nice.              - Yeah.
-我被感動了       -我這可是發自內心的
- I'm touched.                - Yeah. Just from the heart.
-好吧，但我沒說我哪裡被感動了                   -你真是的
- Well, I didn't tell you where I was touched.                                               - Oh, you!
天  一切結束後我們該何去何從
Oh, God. What are we gonna do when this is over?
自力更生吧  計劃書上就只寫到這次表演結束
We're on our own. Our instructions run out after the show.
就算"魔眼"並不存在
Even if there is no "Eye,"
即使我們被人徹底耍了，還要坐20年的牢
if we were completely played and we spend the next 20 years in jail, then,
但我只是想說
I just want to say that...
我懂  我也是
I know. Me, too.
我可吃不消你們這么煽情
Little too sentimental for me.
他們在那兒
There they are!
去抓住他們  快  快  快  抓住他們
Go grab 'em! Put 'em down! Go, go, go! Grab 'em!
-起來      -怎么回事
- Get up!       - What the hell?
該死
Shit!
你好  紐約
Hello, New York!
感謝魔術
Thank you for the magic.
同樣感謝你們這些偉大而忠實的觀眾
And thank you for being such an incredible and dedicated audience.
可惜的是  天下沒有不散的筵席
Unfortunately, like all good things, it must come to an end.
因此今晚在開始表演之前
So we would like to start our show tonight...
我們向大家說聲再見
By saying goodbye.
我們將為世界展示一場魔術盛典
All we wanted was to bring the world to a magic show.
從而把一些魔法帶回到這個世間
And thereby bring a little magic back to the world.
讓開
Clear the way!
這一路上  我們走得很艱辛
This has been one hell of a ride for all of us.
但現在到了該說再見的時刻了
But it's time for us to disappear.
晚安  紐約
Good night, New York.
感謝你們一直相信我們
And thank you for believing in us.
停下
Stop!
別跑
Freeze!
別開槍
No!
該死的
God damn it!
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你是對的  這件事遠比我們所有人都重要
You were right. It's bigger than all of us.
但我這次我並不快樂
This is one time I'm not happy being right.
這事估計就此結束了吧
So I guess this is it.
是嗎
Is it?
迪倫... 迪倫  迪倫...
Dylan! Dylan! Dylan!
-你看          -這是甚麼
- You see that?                 - What?
那麼真的錢在哪裡呢？
Where's the real money?
你被捕了  舉起手來  快
You're under arrest! Hands in the air! Now!
快訊、爆炸新聞：聯邦調查局跟丟四騎士，四騎士在紐約下起了美金雨
我是被陷害的
I've been framed.
-沒人說不是       -我能證明我是被陷害的
- I'm sure you were.                     - Yeah, but I can prove it.
我經常拆穿這種把戲  就如同我預測你一直在干蠢事一樣
I always do. Just like I predicted that you'd play the fool.
我們把那些戲劇成份都拋開，好嗎？
Let's just drop the theatricality, all right?
又不是在拍電影
The cameras aren't rolling in here.
-伙計們  我能和他單獨呆一會嗎                 -可以
- Fellas, can I have a few minutes with my friend here alone, please.               - Sure.
好了  我把真相分析給你聽
All right. I got information to trade.
-作為交易  你放我走  怎麼樣？         -如果這是物有所值的話
- I believe that's how it's done. Huh?                                    - If it's of some value.
在這裡讓我有充足的時間來思考
These bars give a man time to think.
現在我知道她們是如何做到這一切的
And I'm pretty sure I know how they did it.
你還記得第二次演出中那個兔子魔術嗎？
Remember the rabbit trick in the second show?
那個盒子並不是空的
The box was never empty.
而那個倉庫的房間也不是空的
The room wasn't either.
當騎士們進入倉庫後
After gaining access to the warehouse,
他們並沒有移走保險箱
The Horsemen left the real safe
只是把整個屋子變成了一個特大號的兔子盒
and transformed the whole room into a giant rabbit box.
你們衝進去後  感覺保險箱已經不見了
You go charging in there, thinking the safe was already gone.
停下
Hey! Stop!
你們又被耍了
Missing the trick. Again.
這讓你們理所當然的認為保險箱已經被偷了
Which was to make you think the safe had already been stolen,
于是你放松警惕並離開了
so you'd drop your guard and leave.
然而當你忙著追假的保險箱時
Now, while you were busy playing with balloon animals,
有人闖入了倉庫
someone was breaking into the warehouse.
誰
Who?
杰克·瓦爾德
Jack Wilder.
我的天
Holy shit.
不可能  我親眼看著他死的
No. No way. He died right in front of my eyes.
如果... 其實他沒死
Unless, of course, he didn't.
這裡鎖住了
It's locked.
你們忘記了嗎
Weren't you listening?
沒有我打不開的鎖
Nothing's ever locked.
干的漂亮  瓦爾德先生  太棒了
Well done, Mr. Wilder! Good work.
你已經可以獨當一面了  杰克
You're a big boy now, Jack.
他開著一輛聯邦調查局的車逃跑了  對嗎
He escaped in a standard FBI vehicle, right?
然後把把你們領到大橋上
Led you to the bridge.
而其他騎士已經帶著輛一模一樣的備用車在那兒等著了
Where the other Horsemen were waiting with an identical replacement car.
在你的視線失去追蹤目標的那瞬間
It only took a split second
他們把車子掉包了
for you to lose contact with it and make the switch.
當你爬進那輛著火的車裡時
When you crawled into that burning car,
我不得不說  你的舉動十分英勇
quite heroically, I might add,
但卻因為解救一具從太平間偷來的尸體而險些喪命
you almost died trying to rescue what I assume was a cadaver from the morgue.
他們為甚麼煞費苦心實施如此危險的計劃
Why go through such an elaborate and dangerous plan
難道只是為了陷害一個人？
just to frame one guy?
我不知道
I don't know.
他們從不拿取任何財物
They never kept any of the money they took.
這點我也還沒想通
Yeah, that's the part I haven't been able to put together yet.
我剛才只是給了你一些很重要的信息
But I just gave you information that is substantially more important.
-其實沒有           -甚麼
- No. Not really.                    - What?
我終于有機會詳細的調查萊昂納爾·施萊克
I finally got a chance to really look into Lionel Shrike.
弄清了他複出的原因，以及那次事故的緣由
His comeback attempt. His accident.
那家拒絕賠償的保險公司
The insurer who denied the family's claim?
就是特萊斯勒保險公司
Tressler Insurance.
而持有相關票據的那家銀行
The bank that carried the note?
也正是巴黎信貸共和銀行
Credit Republican of Paris.
巴黎信貸共和銀行
Credit Republicain de Paris.
信貸共和
你怎么解釋這些呢
What do you make of that?
到處都會有笨蛋
A sucker is born every minute.
我們凌晨兩點被指引到中央公園來，萬一被打劫了怎么辦
What if all this was just leading up to us getting mugged in Central Park at 2:00 A.M.?
不會  我感覺我們正是應該來這裡
No, I'm telling you, we're right where we need to be.
-只要找到               -那個嗎
- We just have to find...               - That?
萊昂納爾·施萊克之樹
The Lionel Shrike tree.
還有封在樹中的紙牌
And the card encased in glass.
現在怎么辦
What do we do now?
噢，太美妙了
Oh, nice!
現在我有了一個新的論點
So, here's my new theory.
傳說中的「魔眼」無處不在
The legend is that the "Eye" is everywhere.
他們等待著真正偉大的魔術師  證明自己有別於與平庸之輩
Waiting for the truly great magicians to distinguish themselves from the mediocre ones.
可能你就是平庸中的一員
Maybe that was you.
你的內心深處強烈的渴望成為「魔眼」的一份子  只是他們從未邀請你加入
Deep down inside you wanted nothing more than to be part of the "Eye", But you were never invited.
因此你試圖摧毀他們  但結果呢
So you try to destroy them. But instead what happens?
你惹怒了他們
You pissed them off.
「魔眼」是不存在的
The Eye isn't real.
那麼  你解釋給我聽  誰是幕後主謀
Okay, then, explain then. Who's behind all this?
-某個喪心病狂、思路縝密的人           -誰
- Somebody with an obsession... meticulous...         - Who?
一個孤注一擲的人
Somebody prepared to sacrifice everything.
以至於他在花招耍完之前都不會被懷疑
Somebody so prepared to lose that they wouldn't even be a suspect until the trick was done.
不用講多  直接告訴我名字  他是誰
I don't want a profile. I need a name. Who? Who?
我不知道是誰
I don't know who.
但他們一定是進入了倉庫  並安置好了鏡子
But they had to have access to the warehouse to plant the mirrors.
他們總是比我和聯邦調查局的人搶先一步
Always a step ahead of me. And the FBI.
他們一次、兩次、接連戲耍警察
Got past them not once, not twice, but consistently.
好像他們就一直是在...
Almost as if they were on the...
我們內部
The inside.
-你          -嗯
- You.                   - Hm.
為甚麼
Why?
很難想通，是嗎？
That is the question, isn't it?
你猜對了
You're right.
你根本不知道  為了看到你現在臉上的表情  我已經等了多久
I can't tell you how long I've waited to see the look on your face.
你是誰
Who are you?
你想從我這裡得到甚麼
What do you want from me?
我想要甚麼？
What do I want?
我只是要你一輩子都呆在這個牢房裡
I want you to spend the rest of your life in this cell,
面壁思過  反省你的所作所為
staring at four walls and wondering how you missed it.
你是如何由於過於自我而被矇蔽了雙眼
How you let yourself be so blinded by your ego
在你自認為先人一步的時候
that you convinced yourself that you were one step ahead
你其實卻落後於別人兩步
when you were always two steps behind.
迪倫
Dylan?
等等
Wait a minute.
迪倫  這到底是怎么回事
Dylan! How did this happen?
迪倫  為甚麼
Dylan! Why?
為甚麼
Why?
我的天
Oh, my God.
我可沒料到這個
I did not see that coming.
這不可能
That's impossible!
不會吧
No way.
實際上還不錯啦
That was actually pretty good.
謝謝
Thank you.
當我說「永遠是屋子裡最聰明的人」時
When I said, "Always be the smartest guy in the room."
我和你意見一致
We were in agreement.
那就好
Okay. Right.
亨莉
Henley.
我還沒見過她會無語
I've never seen her speechless.
那我就當這是在夸我了
I take that as a huge compliment.
伙計  抱歉揍了你  真心抱歉
Hey, man, I'm so sorry for kicking your ass. Really.
說正經的  我一直很相信魔法
Hey, listen, for the record, I have always been a 100% believer.
而且我還花了不少精力
And the amount of energy I have expended to keep
讓這些不信的人去相信
these infidels on point...
梅利特  你可以加入
Merritt, you're in.
上帝保佑
God bless.
來吧
Come.
真正的魔法是將四個強大的個體匯聚在一起而發揮的作用
The real magic is taking four strong solo acts and making them all work together.
而你們正是這樣做的
And that's exactly what you did.
所以... 歡迎
So welcome.
歡迎加入「魔眼」
Welcome to the Eye.
困死于水底
重現偉大魔術失敗  偉大的施萊克消失在河流中
大型魔術成為施萊克致命的閉幕演出  搜救隊無法找到其遺體
一切的確是有聯系的
It was all connected.
信貸共和銀行  特萊斯勒保險公司
Credit Republican. Tressler Insurance.
你好
Bonjour.
埃爾克霍恩呢
And Elkhorn?
他和施萊克有甚麼關系
What's the connection to Shrike?
埃爾克霍恩最初是魔術安全箱生產商
Elkhorn started as a safe manufacturer.
但他們使用偷工減料的鋼材
They used cheap steel.
因為拿回扣的關係...
They cut corners.
當施萊克沉到河底時  安全箱變形了NWhen he got to the bottom of the river, the safe warped.
他被困在裡面了
And he was trapped.
他是你父親
He was your father.
演出前的早晨我覺得有些異樣
The morning before the show didn't feel like any other day.
父親說他必須去工作的時候
When my father said he had to go to work,
他看得出我不愿意他離開
he could see that I didn't want him to leave.
因此他把他的手表留給我
So he gave me his watch,
讓我數著時間等他回來
and he told me to count the seconds until he came back.
我從未讓表停走過
I have never let his watch stop since then.
從此以後
And from that moment on,
戴了一張面具來生活
I created a persona.
我計劃著  算好了所有細節
I planned. I worked out every detail.
但我唯一沒有算到的
But the one thing that I couldn't imagine happening
就是你
was you.
對你來說  最合理的做法
And I know that the logical conclusion for you
就是努力解決這個案件
is to take this case to its resolution.
把我供出去
And for you to turn me in.
沒錯
Yeah.
你知道我是怎么看待決心和邏輯的
But you know how I feel about resolution and logic.
你也知道我認為
And you also know
有些事還是不要過多解釋的好
that I think some things are best left unexplained.
又是一個要鎖起來的秘密
One more secret to lock away.
靠近些
Come in close.
再近些
Closer.
現在你知道我們的秘密了
Because now you know our secret.
我們無處不在  我們注視著你
We could be anywhere. Watching you.
我們在為下一個魔術招募人才
We're looking for someone to help us with our next trick.
數到三  睜開眼
On the count of three, open your eyes
告訴我你看到了甚麼
and tell me what you see.
一
One.
二
Two...
拜托  停車  停車
Please, stop, stop, stop.
好了  停下來  把車停下來
All right, stop the van. Stop the van.
我要跳車了
I'm gonna jump out of the van.
終于到了
Oh, thank God.
我們在哪
Where are we?
真好  又到了個鬼地方
Great, another shit hole.
好了  感受一下吧
Okay, feeling it.
我累死了  餓死了而且很不爽
I'm exhausted, and hungry, and cranky.
看看這個地方
Check out this place.
-這是甚麼地方  -這就是一個垃圾場
- Where'd you bring us? - Was there no landfill where we were?
這地方太棒了
This place is awesome.
這是我們的新工具嗎
Is this our new gear?
這兒最好別有甚麼連衣褲
There'd better not be, like, matching jumpsuits in there.
我不穿緊身衣的
You know I don't wear spandex.
-鎖上了  -大伙  得用卡片來開箱子
-It's locked. - Guys, the cards.
-甚麼卡片  -你甚麼意思
- What card? - What do you mean, "What card"?
好吧
Okay.